One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
He won!
Arlong Park has fallen!
We did it, older sister!
Gen!
This... This isn't a dream, right?
I never thought this day would come.
Way to go, Luffy! I'll throw in my compliments, too!
Though, I'd praise you even more,
if you would've given me more of a starring role!
Man, talk about being on pins and needles.
Next time, wrap it up a bit quicker, you damn jerk!
This is awesome!
All right, that's enough of that!
It's that guy...!
What a lucky day today is!
Well done.
I watched the entire fight.
Fluke or not, I never once imagined the fishmen would lose
to a band of no-name pirates like you.
However, thanks to you,
all the money I was to give Arlong
and anything of value found in Arlong Park is now mine!
Everyone drop your weapons!
The credit for this incident now belongs
to me, Captain Nezumi of the Navy 16th Branch!
Zoro!
Don't rain on people's parade while they're rejoicing!
J-Just you try to lay a finger on me! You'll be sorry!
Are you still talking?
This is for shooting Nojiko...
and for tearing up Bell-mère's tangerine orchard.
Huh?
Captain!
Thanks, Nami! That felt good!
Give 'im 1,000 more of those!
You marines are gonna clean up
after these fishmen now!
And you're gonna help rebuild the town of Gosa!
And you're not gonna touch
anything of value in Arlong Park!
That's the island's money! Got it?!
Ow! Ow! I-I'll do what you say!
And one other thing!
Give me my money back!
I'll give it back! I'll give it back!
It's not worth it anymore!
I'll get you, you rotten pirates!
Straw hat man!
Your name's Luffy, right?!
You're the captain, right?!
Remember this!
You're in for quite the ride!
You've pushed me too far!
It's too late for regrets!
I will have my revenge!
Just you wait and see!
He says we're in for quite the ride.
How does he know I'm gonna be king of the pirates?
That's not what he means!
Man, you're stupid!
H-Hey, what do we do?! What if we really do wind up in big trouble?!
Hey! Hey! What'll we do?!
Alright, everyone!
We can't have all the fun!
Everyone on the island needs to know about this monumental event!
Arlong Park...
Arlong Park has fallen!
Good for you, Nami!
I can't believe we were saved by pirates.
Life's full of surprises.
Headquarters?! Navy Headquarters?!
Hello! This is Captain Nezumi of the 16th Branch!
Marine code 00733!
I have a request for HQ!
Listen! There's a pirate named Luffy,
who wears a straw hat!
You don't need to shout.
I can hear you.
I deem him and his four crew members enemies of the government!
"Luffy."
They managed to take down
the purportedly invincible Arlong Pirates,
the fishmen of Arlong Park!
Considering this threat, I have placed
a hefty bounty on the captain, Straw Hat Luffy!
I'm now sending a photograph!
Roger that.
Huh?!
Couldn't you have taken a better one?!
No, that's all I could get.
After a quick verification,
I will submit it for approval.
Don't forget, now!
He's a vile pirate! "Dead or Alive"!
Put him on wanted posters across the globe!
He's still at it.
Sounds like ol' Zoro's really hurtin'.
Well, yeah.
An average person with those wounds would take two years to fully heal!
You moron!
Trying to take care of such a grave injury on your own!
Oww!
Honestly! Are you folks really pirates?!
Do you even have...
a ship's doctor?!
A doctor? That sounds good, too!
Luffy?
But a musician comes first.
Right, Zoro?
Why's that?!
Because pirates sing, you know!
So why does that come first?!
Hey, Doctor. Where's Nami?
She doesn't seem to be here, either.
Nami, huh?
If you can't find her around,
then she's probably where she always goes.
What?! You're still here, Nami?
Your friends've been looking for you, you know.
Hey, Nojiko... Gen.
If Bell-mère were alive,
do you think she'd stop me from being a pirate?
A pirate?!
Give me a break!
There's no way she'd ever let
her precious daughter be a pirate!
She wouldn't stop you!
Nojiko!
Even if she tried,
would you really listen to her?
Absolutely not!
Whew, I'm stuffed!
Sometimes it's nice to just eat!
Are your wounds all better now, Zoro?
This's nothin'! Some food and drink'll fix it right up!
Yeah?
But how long is this dumb party gonna last?
This is the third day now!
What's wrong with that?
When you wanna celebrate,
you should pull out all the stops.
Hey, Sanji!
That melon you just had!
Was there something on it?!
What's with all that meat?!
Sure was. It's prosciutto and melon, so there was prosciutto on it.
Prosciutto and melon?! That sounds great! Wh-Where did you get it?!
Dunno.
The whole village is a buffet party,
so I dunno where I got it.
He's long gone.
He's been eating non-stop for three days straight!
Now, then. I'm done eating.
Now I think I'll...
pick up some girls!
Way to go, kiddo!
Can I have your autograph?!
I am Captain Usopp,
the lovable and courageous hero,
who brought down the strongest fishman officer of all!
Here's an Usopp anthem!
Who was it? Who was it?
Who beat the fishman?
Hmph. How boring.
What is?
I thought you'd be more down in the dumps.
Like, "Why didn't this happen before my dad died?!"
That's how I felt at first.
But now I'm thinking about the future.
The future?
That straw hat guy and his friends helped us out.
But tomorrow, we need to make a fresh start by ourselves.
There's no way we can forget the past,
and I don't think we need to.
But what's important is what comes next!
What should we do?
What do we need to do?
We're the ones who're gonna sustain our villages now.
That's the approach I'm gonna take.
You're so precocious!
Oww!
Why're you pinching me?!
I don't understand! Why?!
And here I was just hoping to tease you again!
You've teased me plenty,
you dumb, tattooed punk girl!
I'm okay with "punk"!
Will it come off?
I'd like to say, "No problem,"
but there's no way to remove it altogether.
There'll be some scarring.
That's how tattoos are.
Yeah. I know it's stupid of me.
They're there for life.
I don't want anyone to see this!
This... this tattoo...
I don't even want to be
in Arlong's crew,
but it's like I've been
branded a pirate!
Nami.
Nojiko! What is that?!
Oh? You mean this?
It's no big deal!
It's just a decoration!
Now I'm just like you!
Say, Doctor.
There's a tattoo I'd like to have.
Here.
Those two can dance!
Here's Usopp Anthem No. 185!
Bell-mère,
your girls have grown up to be positively tough and honorable!
They remind me of you.
We're going to live life to its fullest from now on.
We've lost and sacrificed far too much.
Which is why we're gonna smile and laugh like the idiots we are!
Prosciutto and melon!
Huh? There's no food around here.
That's no good. Time to go back.
Hold it, boy!
A grave? Did someone die?
Yeah. A long time ago.
Oh, my deepest conveniences.
Huh? Deepest concussions.
Huh? Deepest compli–
Deepest condolences.
That's what I meant.
Hey, boy.
Nami is going aboard your ship.
She's going to be a pirate.
It'll be a dangerous journey.
If you guys ever do anything to take away her smile,
I will kill you!
Yeah. I'm not gonna do that, though.
Got it?!
I got it!
This the last of it?
Yeah!
Alright!
Are you finished loading it all?
Yeah!
Now, then. We got loads of provisions now.
We're good to go.
We were only here a few days,
but we made tons of memories
on this island, huh?
Yeah!
We owe you so much for everything you've done.
We're gonna get back to bounty hunting again!
This is goodbye for now,
but we look forward to the day we meet again somewhere!
Take care!
You guys, too!
Well, we should get going, too!
Hey! Hold on!
What about Nami?!
Maybe she's not coming?
Why not?!
You! You made another pass
at Nami, didn't you?!
Why would I do that?
Oh, yeah. She achieved her goal,
No, you definitely did!
and she has no reason to be a pirate,
You can't stand that Nami
and I are all lovey-dovey!
so she might be happier here.
Are you an idiot?
What'd you call me?!
What about my happiness?!
If Nami isn't on the ship,
then 98.72% of my reason for being here is gone!
By the way, I couldn't find
the prosciutto and melon anywhere!
Hey! Where's Nacchan?
That's the thing!
Nobody's seen her since this morning!
What?! She's leaving all the money behind?!
The 100 million belly?!
She left it in our house, along with a letter.
She's planning to travel without her money?!
But she risked her life to earn it!
She says it's okay,
because she'll just steal some more.
Once that girl says something,
there's no changing her mind.
That fool! We're the ones who still have so much to thank her for!
Nami!
Nacchan!
Set sail!
Huh? She's started sprinting!
She says to set sail.
Wait!
Does she really intend to leave
without letting us thank her or say goodbye?!
You can't be serious!
Hoist the sails!
H-Hey!
They're setting sail!
Wait! We still haven't thanked you!
Stop, Nacchan!
At least let us thank you!
Nacchan!
Hold it! I won't let you leave like this!
Hey, is this how we should let them say goodbye?
Why not? It's her decision.
Nami!
Why?!
She didn't!
– What's this...?!
– My wallet's gone!
Mine, too!
Same here!
Take care, everyone!
How dare you!
You damn brat!
Hey, she hasn't changed a bit.
Who knows when she'll betray us again.
Nami! Good job!
You lousy pickpocket!
Get back here!
Give back our wallets!
You punk!
Come back anytime!
Take care of yourself!
We're grateful to you guys!
Boy!
Don't forget your promise!
Bye, everyone!
I'm heading out!
She got us good!
My little sister's gonna do great!
Enjoy yourself!
Here, Genzo.
What's this scrap of paper, Doctor?
That silly girl. She never learns.
She got another tattoo before she left.
What is this symbol?
It's a tangerine and a pinwheel, apparently.
Oh? Gen!
What happened to your pinwheel?
I doubt there's any need for it now.
I'm heading out!
Hold on, Gen-san!
Stay away from Nami!
No, but, I want to see her smile, too!
She starts crying because you have such a scary face!
But what am I supposed to do about that?
I know!
This'll make you laugh, right?!
If I always keep it here like this?!
What do you say, Nami-chan?
Look. I really don't think a dumb pinwheel is going to make Nami...
Oh. She laughed.