One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
The problem is, the World Government...
doesn't just want to get rid
of Stella, but me, too!
I can't believe them! This sucks!
They'll pay for this, right?!
Well, say something!
Yes, they'll pay for this.
Too slow!
But if that's what they're up to, I have a plan!
So...
First things first, I need you guys
to take care of all these pests!
I locked down the Frontier Dome,
so kill everyone other than me, Stella,
and the hostages underground!
Understood!
And while you're running amok,
they'll start to wonder who ordered you.
If I'm busted...
there's no way I'll be able to stand up to them!
S-Snake!
Yes, ma'am.
I need you to put on a show
and pretend you got me.
Yes, ma'am.
And make sure to undo it
when no one's looking!
Yes, ma'am!
Also, there's one part of
the lab you need to leave alone.
This goes for all of you.
So listen carefully...
Let the hunt...
begin!
Hurry up! Everyone, get on the ship!
We've got to get off of Egghead!
Are you punks...
ready to rock?
– Yeah!
Listen up, Kid Pirates!
Our chief is Red-Haired Shanks, you know...
You've got no ribbit to see– I-I mean...
He misspoke!
...you've got no right to see him!
He'f wight!
Pops, your dentures!
Yeah! Dummies!
I hate you!
I will...
never ever...
let you see Chiefy!
You're so brave, Princess!
Is this a joke?!
I toad you to leave!
These are Red Hair's allies?!
I'll never lose to you!
I thought we were in the New World!
I get what you're saying,
but there are some big names here, too.
Don't let your guard down.
I won't hold back even if
they're nobodies, but...
We're gonna set sail soon!
Chief!
They went to stop the Kid Pirates!
Tell them to pull back!
Before they get hurt!
– Whoa, whoa, whoa!
– Wait, wait, wait!
– What are you talking about, Chief?!
I... What are you guys doing?!
I won't let them lay a finger on you!
– Yeah!
Well, I really appreciate the offer!
But stay away from the sea.
Hey, get off me already!
Don't go!
Let us fight, too!
Come on, guys...
Say it ain't so!
Chief, you leavin' already?
Yeah, Chief!
We only just got to see you!
Sorry about that.
We only swung by on
our way to somewhere else.
Now come on, let go.
We stayed so long, a big shot found us.
Oh, and like I said...
tell the ships to pull back!
Our allies are famously weak after all.
Weak, huh?! You cheeky bastard!
We're still alive thanks to you!
Your flag is what protects us!
Yeah!
Worry less about fighting
and more about aging, Granny Oli.
Oh, put a sock in it, Chief!
You're as popular as ever, Chief!
Oh, please...
Don't worry, Chief. We'll take care of him.
Hey now, he's worth three billion.
Don't underestimate how fast kids grow up.
But have their wounds
from Wano healed already?
Yeah.
They look fine to me.
They're all ready for a scrap.
That's good...
Any updates on Blackbeard?
Nah, just that he definitely
left the Pirate Island.
I thought for sure he'd show up in Wano.
Hongo!
Here. The intel on Captain Kid.
That's our Hongo! Always prepared!
Shut it! Keep loading!
So he's from the South Blue, huh?
He's been going pretty wild...
How many ships are there?
Nine.
I've seen some of these faces
on wanted posters.
Ribbit?!
I don't give a damn who I'm facing!
I'll wipe 'em out in ten seconds flat!
With this...
Damned Punk!
Is the ship getting pulled?!
What is that?!
A cannon?!
I don't waste time with fodder!
To anyone...
who stands in our way...
Get blown to hell!
Show yourself!
Red Hair!
Shit!
Tell the fleet to spread out!
What's wrong, Chief?!
Dorry! Brogy! Get ready!
– Alright!
Hard to port!
There'll be too much damage...
Guess he saw a pretty nasty future.
Get blown to hell!
Just as I thought.
Red Hair!
Divine Departure.
Partner.
Yeah.
Just a bit farther.
Yeah!
We won!
Just one more lode poneglyph!
One more and I'll be the King of the Pirates!
Kaido! Big Mom! Red Hair!
They're all washed-up fossils!
We're the strongest!
No one can keep up with us!
The one to be King of the Pirates...
will be me!
Killer, you bastard!
Why are you laughi–
Boss...
Boss!
Open your eyes!
Kid!
Hey, Kid!
Boss!
He's not moving!
He's gonna die!
Dammit!
Killer got hurt covering him, too!
We surrender, Red Hair!
Please help us!
Don't kill our boss!
Hey, Emma, bring them here!
What?
Hurry up!
Th-These are our lode poneglyphs!
This is all we got!
Please spare our lives!
Chief! This way!
H-Hey...
Look at the island!
Something really bad...
is coming!
Hey, puny humans!
If you point a cannon at
someone else's home...
...don't be surprised when they fire back!
Dominion!
At Elbaph, in the New World...
the Kid Pirates, led by Eustass "Captain" Kid...
a man with a bounty of three billion berries...
were destroyed.
Several Hours Ago...
Warland, Elbaph
New World
Captain "Frog-Toes" Gerotini
Puddle Pirates
Bandmaster Fuga "the Addenturer"
Social Club
Pururu "the Brr-rave"
Bourgeois Pirates