One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Wow... An elephant bluefin tuna, huh?
Ahhh! I can't wait to cook it!
Ah! That was fun!
Huh?
What's the matter, Nami?
There was a shift in the air...
The air?
It's gonna rain.
Huh? When the weather is this nice?
There's no doubt about it.
Hey, someone's on
the execution platform!
Who the heck is that?
That old man said that the King of
the Pirates died here twenty-two years ago.
He showed up?!
Yes! We watched over the square as ordered,
and then the man from the wanted poster...!
Okay.
Let's go flashily.
He walked right up to it...
Just you wait, brat.
Wow! So this what it looked like
for the King of the Pirates...
Please wait!
Captain Smoker!
Come along, Tashigi.
Hey! You up there!
Come down this instant!
Why?!
That's a special execution platform
used by the World Government!
Come down right now!
Hmph! Now's not
the time for small fries.
Hm?
I've been looking for you, Luffy.
Long time no see...
Don't tell me you've forgotten my face.
How pretty!
She's stunning!
She's a woman of unrivaled beauty!
Her skin looks so smooth.
I don't know anyone like you.
Who the heck are you?
I'll never forget you...
because you're the first man
to have ever hit me.
What? I hit you?
When your passionate fist struck me...
Oh, it felt great...
Fellas... On these seas,
who's the fairest of them all?
– That'd be you!
That's right. It's me.
There isn't a man in this world
that doesn't bow before my beauty.
And I do love a strong man.
I'll make you mine, Luffy.
Shut up!
No way! Who the heck are you?
Still haven't figured it out?!
This is the police! Come quietly, lady!
You're under arrest for
assaulting our police captain!
And you! Get off
the execution platform!
Oh? Who'd you say you'd arrest?
Lieutenant, we have
a problem! She's beautiful!
Beauty be damned! Arrest her!
Sh-She's so beautiful
that she's dazzling!
How nice!
We're being bombed!
She'll get hit!
Wh-What the...?!
The fountain slid right past...!
What just happened?!
That was dangerous, you know.
Flashily sorry. But your smooth skin is
unharmed, of course. So no harm done...
fairest Alvida!
Huh? Alvida?
I don't see Alvida.
I'm Alvida, you blockhead!
Really? You don't look like her at all...
I changed after eating a devil fruit.
The name of the fruit is...
the Smooth-Smooth Fruit!
All attacks slide right off my skin
and leave me unharmed.
Unfortunately, my beauty
couldn't be improved that much.
There was one big change, though.
Why, yes, my freckles are gone.
N-No, that's not really what I meant.
After becoming a new person,
I teamed up with a certain someone
because he also wanted to find you.
Now, the main star can
make his flashy entrance!
Monkey D. Luffy!
Since the day you sent me flying,
I've been obsessed with
getting revenge on you.
That alone led me to
finally find my crew.
It was indeed a great adventure.
I was missing parts of my body.
I laughed, I went through hell,
and I made new friends.
I call it "Little Buggy's Big Adventure."
You see, Buggy was...
Why am I telling you any of this?!
What? Wait, what
was your name again?
Bogey... No, Boogie.
Maybe it was Behee...? Or not...
Oh, yeah!
Buffoon!
Buffoon?! Stop messing around!
You're as irritating as ever, you moron!
Th-That's Buggy the Clown!
They're p-pirates!
It's the Buggy Pirates!
People! Remain flashily where you are!
I'm gonna show you all
just how scary I am.
Oh! It's Buggy!
You just remembered it?!
Wh-What's going on?
Long time no see, rubber man.
How's Roronoa Zoro doing?
Okay, Cabaji. Good job.
I ask that my hundreds of billions of
followers around the world watch closely!
We're about to host a super
flashy public execution!
Monkey D. Luffy! You can't
move even an inch now.
You should feel honored, Straw Hat!
You get to die in the same place
as the King of the Pirates.
The atmospheric pressure
is dropping like crazy.
I've never seen such
a bizarre drop before.
Now that you mention it,
the wind does feel different...
A storm is gonna hit this island!
A-A storm?
We'd better hurry back to
the ship or we'll be in trouble.
Will it be a big one?
Hey...!
Hm?
Zoro!
Have you seen him?
You mean Luffy?
– Pirates are here!
Pirates are here!
Run!
It's Buggy the Clown!
What'd they say?!
Buggy the Clown!
What? Then...
Y-Yes, sir!
In addition to Straw Hat Luffy,
Buggy the Clown and Iron Club Alvida,
both being notorious East Blue pirates,
have arrived to take over the square!
Right under my nose...
What arrogant scum.
What should we do, Captain Smoker?
Unit one will set up on the sea!
Unit two will secretly surround
the square in the streets.
The rest will stand by within
firing range of the square.
That is all!
Yes, sir!
Give this order to unit one.
Yes sir?
"Destroy any pirate ships
as soon as you see them.
Don't let any pirates off
this island. Not a single one."
An execution!
An execution is starting!
Buggy the Clown will be
executing Straw Hat Luffy!
Luffy's gonna be executed?!
That idiot!
Let's go!
Take care of this!
S-S-S-Sanji!
Treat it like a lady! Got it?!
Oops!
We have to hurry, too!
Hey! Hey, N-N-Nami! Where're we going?!
The harbor, of course!
Th-The harbor? Oh, makes sense!
Captain Smoker! Please take a look.
Things are getting weird.
Hm?
Wha...! Th-That kid...!
What's he doing?
Monkey D. Luffy. This can't be!
It looks like he's about to be killed!
Captain, are we
swooping in right away?
Idiot. Don't be hasty.
A pirate is about to kill another pirate.
This is great. They're
saving us the trouble.
Listen up! Once Straw Hat's head rolls,
surround Buggy, Alvida,
and those with them!
Don't give 'em time to think!
Pirate Monkey D. Luffy is a criminal
and will be flashily executed for...
pissing me off with his attitude!
Live it up flashily!
This is my first time
seeing an execution.
We're executing you.
Hm?
What?! Stop joking!
You stop joking!
Take this board off! You bastard!
And now, the public execution
will flashily commence!
Take it off! You tricked me!
You're a jerk! You bastard!
Ahhh!! Stop it! Ahhh!
I don't wanna die!
There's a big cumulus cloud
in the sky to the east!
A storm is coming. It's
gonna be unimaginably big...
If Buggy, Luffy, and the others
go crazy, the Marines will take action.
We're done for if the ship is washed
out to sea when we have to escape.
Yeah, this is urgent!
The Marines may have
already made their move.
The Going Merry is in danger!
Th-The Going Merry
will end up in Marine hands?
Come on, Nami! H-Hurry up!
Wait for me!
Hurry to the harbor!
♪ Riding around on the Richie Bike! ♪
♪ Who's that man?
Who? Who? Who's that man?! ♪
♪ Me! ♪
So this is the rubber guy's ship...
It's bigger than his first,
like he's a real pirate...
It's about time for him to get
flashily executed by Captain Buggy!
However...! Just in case the rubber guy,
who has no chance of escaping,
happens to escape...
♪ It's our duty to burn this ship! ♪
I'm sorry. I won't do it again.
Please let me go.
Why would I do that, idiot?!
Hmph! This is what happens
when someone goes against us.
I guess this is it for
the man I had my eye on...
Since you have a big audience,
do you wanna say
something before you die?
No? Well, that's okay.
It wouldn't matter anyway
since you're about to die.
I'm the man who's gonna be
King of the Pirates!
Wha...?
D-Did he just say
"King of the Pirates"?!
In this town, of all places...
What a crazy thing to say...
Well then, I guess this is it...
you rubber twerp.
Stop...
Wh-What?
– ...the execution!
What?
Zoro! Sanji!
It's Pirate Hunter Z-Zoro!
Zoro?!
Ah, there you are, Zoro!
But you arrived a moment too late!
– We'll bring down...
– ...that execution platform!
Roronoa Zoro...
Guys... get them!
Leave it to us!
Big Sis Alvida!
Out of our way!
Not even Zoro can stop me now!
This is the end of your captain!
Damn bastard!
If I could just cut down the platform...
Listen.
The instant Monkey D. Luffy's head falls,
we're to attack all at once!
All units. Prepare for battle.
– Yes, sir!
Zoro! Sanji!
Usopp! Nami!
Hurry up!
This is heavy!
Sorry.
I'm... dead.
Idiot...!
Don't say something so stupid!
He smiled!
I'm still alive!
Neat!
H-Hey, do you believe in God?
Phew, lucky me.
Stop talking nonsense.
Let's get out of this town already!
I was worried for a moment.
It's just one thing after another.
Now! Corner the pirates!
– Yeah!
Here they come!
Amazing! Amazing!
It's suddenly gotten crazy!
Amazing! Ahh! Amazing!
Hey, Luffy!
Ahhh... Z-Zoro!
I get that this is exciting,
but we've gotta go!
We'd better hurry back to the ship or
we'll never be able to leave the island.
We won't be able to
enter the Grand Line!
What?! That's not good!
The Straw Hats are running!
Capture them!
Go after them!
Why did he smile?
Did he know he'd be saved?
No. In that moment, he genuinely
thought his life was over.
He was prepared
to accept death and smiled.
Captain, we have to
apprehend the pirates.
Hey... have you seen a pirate who
smiled on the execution platform?
N-Never! Even if they're acting tough,
at the moment of death,
they all turn pale and die in despair.
That man in the straw hat smiled...
just like the Pirate King, twenty-two years ago in this town...
Gold Roger smiled on
the execution platform.
Captain...
Where did Straw Hat go?
He ran toward the sea, sir.
What's unit one doing? They should've
destroyed their ship by now.
Well... They had to return for
refitting because they couldn't
light the gunpowder
due to the sudden rain...
What?!
A reserve unit is currently
moving to attack the ship instead.
Captain Smoker! If we let them set
sail now, they'll enter the Grand Line!
The wind is blowing westward... Their ship will have a tailwind.
Are these all coincidences?
It's as if the heavens have
plans for that young man.
We'd better hurry
or we'll be in trouble!
We're gonna make it
to the Grand Line like this!
I'm White Hound Smoker.
On my honor as a Marine Headquarters
captain, I won't let that man leave this island!
What's with this storm?!
If we don't leave soon,
we'll be stuck here.
Nami's right that we should
hurry back to the ship!
Attacking me is a waste of time.
There isn't a man alive
who can touch my smooth skin.
I just saw a field of flowers...
Captain Buggy, you're alive!
No way I'd die!
Buggy, this isn't good!
Marines from HQ
aren't going to give up.
Hmph. Like I care where
the Marines stick their nose...
Whose nose did you say
is sticking out?!
I didn't say anything like that!
What's the plan?!
Gum-Gum! Go after Gum-Gum!
Mohji and Richie will have
burned down his ship by now.
He can't get off of this island.
We'll kick his ass
and leave this island, guys!
– Yeah!
Motor!
– Yes, Captain!
Chop-Chop Buggy!
Here we go!
Igniting the bomb engine!
Set the slope!
– Yes, Big Sis Alvida!
No Friction...
Smooth-Smooth Tracks!
Don't let the pirates get away!
Wh... What's this smoke?!
What the hell...?!
White Out!
Smoker!
I don't have time for you small fries!
H-He's too strong!
The power of the
Smoke-Smoke Fruit...
He took down Buggy's crew
in a split second...
Fire!
Captain! He caught
us all in one fell swoop!
How dare you, Smoker!
What's with this annoying steel net?!
Firing a weird pistol like that...
The Marines developed this cage shot
as a way to deal with devil fruit powers.
Dammit!
Bring me the Billower Bike!
I'm going after Straw Hat!
Yes, sir!
Dammit!
Why the sudden downpour,
when we've gotta burn this ship down?!
Dammit! This is bad, Richie!
We can't get a fire going like this!
One more time!
Be patient, Richie! I'll feed you later.
What're you doing?!
Mohji!
Oh, if it isn't that thief woman.
Go, Richie!
Lethal Fresh Egg Star!
You...
Damn! The rain made my hand slip!
Richie! Just once, could you not...!
Now! Let's get on the ship!
Yeah!
Hold it! You have to get past me!
I am Mohji, first mate of
Buggy the Clown's pirate crew!
I won't let you set even
one foot aboard this sh–
Prepare to fire!
The Marines!
This is bad!
Aim!
Fire!
Contact the cannon unit!
We'll capture the pirate ship!
Yes, sir!
N-N-N-Nami!
Yeah!
Which direction is the sea?
I can't tell where we're going
because of all this rain!
There they are!
Persistent bastards!
Should we stop and fight?!
We don't have time.
Oh?
Who's that lady?!
Hm?
I didn't realize you were
Roronoa Zoro, and a pirate at that.
You gonna take this sword, too?
You... You lied to me!
What?! What'd you do to her?!
You never asked for my name, is all.
I never lied to you.
Villains like you can't be allowed
to carry a sword of such renown!
I lay claim to the named
blade Wado Ichimonji!
You son of a bitch!
How dare you attack a lady!
Go on ahead.
Let's go.
Hey, Zoro! If you hurt
the lady, I won't forgive you!
Sergeant Major Tashigi!
This is one sword
you won't be getting.
Sergeant Major Tashigi lost...
But she's the Sergeant Major Tashigi...
So long. I'm in a hurry, so...
Why not finish me off?!
Is it because I'm a woman?!
You're lucky, Zoro.
You were born a boy.
Men might be physically
stronger than women,
but it's so insulting that
you won't fight seriously!
There's no way you understand what it
feels like to wish you were born a boy!
I don't carry a sword as an accessory!
I can't stand knowing that you exist!
I'll just tell you! It's your face!
You look exactly like my
good friend who died long ago!
And now you're saying
the same thing she used to!
Who are you to imitate
her, you copycat?!
The hell...?! Grow up
and think before you speak!
I am who I am!
I don't know what your friend was like,
but I'm the one who's upset here!
Maybe she's the copycat!
Wh-What'd you say?!
I see the exit! The harbor is right there!
Hey, who is it now?
You're finally here...
Straw Hat Luffy.
Inherited will...
the tides of time,
and humanity's dreams...
They cannot be stopped.
As long as people seek freedom,
these things will never cease to be.
A pirate, huh? Fine by me.
I'm Captain Smoker.
I run Loguetown for the Marines.
You're under arrest.
Huh? Arrest? Forget it!
I'm on my way to the Grand Line
to become King of the Pirates!
King of the Pirates?
I refuse to get arrested
in a place like this!
Then you'll have to beat me first.
Hey, Luffy...
Sanji, go on ahead. I'll be right there.
Fire!
Fire the cannons!
If we stay here any longer,
the Going Merry will be sunk!
Y-You're about to set sail?
Luffy and them aren't back yet!
We're out of options!
It's better than getting sunk!
Right rudder full!
So what about Luffy's group?
We'll pick them up later!
Don't let them get away! Follow them!
Nami!
Sanji!
Nami, I'm back!
Where're Luffy and Zoro?
Can we even collect
those damn idiots?!
Sanji!
Behind you!
Damn, there's no end to 'em!
I'll cover him! Bring me closer!
I can't! There's a strong current
keeping us from shore!
Ah, screw it!
Usopp!
Bastards!
Usopp! Sanji!
What?! What?! What's going on?!
I ate the Smoke-Smoke Fruit,
so my body become smoke at will!
What's wrong? Had enough?
Gum-Gum Gatling!
What? Eww, that's gross!
White Blow!
You jerk!
Gum-Gum Pistol!
Get it now? You can't
enter the Grand Line.
That's what I'm telling you!
You're wanted for thirty million belly?
Looks like you've run out
of your devil's luck.
Don't be so sure.
You're...
Wh-What's happening? Who is it? Who's there?
The government is after your head.
The world is waiting for our answer.
Th-This is...
Wh-What just happened?
Luffy!
Nami!
We'd better hurry before
the ship is swept away!
Alright!
Gum-Gum...
Wha...?!
W-Wait!
I have a bad feeling...
Rocket!
Ahhh, I knew it!
Everyone...!
Seriously, that flashy gust
was a lucky break.
This escape was possible because
I always keep my wits about me.
Where to now?
Let's head straight to
the Grand Line. How nostalgic!
If that's your decision, then go!
Why?! Why did you help that man...
Dragon?!
What reason would there be to
interfere with a man's departure?
Set sail! We're going after Straw Hat!
What?
We're entering the Grand Line.
B-But, Captain!
This island is your post.
What would the higher-ups say?!
Tell them I said,
"Don't order me around!"
I'm coming with you!
Sergeant Major Tashigi!
I can't let Roronoa get away!
I'll capture him without fail!
Whoa! It feels like
the ship's gonna tip over!
See that light?
The island's lighthouse?
It's a "guiding light."
The entrance to the Grand Line
lies just beyond that light.
The Grand Line is past that light...
What do you wanna do?
D-Do we have to enter
during a storm like this?
Okay, then! Shall we hold a launch
ceremony for entering this great sea?
Hey!
Oh! Sounds good!
Let's do it!
To find the All Blue!
To be King of the Pirates!
To become the greatest swordsman!
To draw a map of the world!
T-To become a brave warrior of the sea!
We're going... to the Grand Line!
– Yeah!