[LUFFY groans]
[LUFFY]
I'm so hungry.
[ZORO]
When the hell are we
gonna reach land anyway?
[LUFFY]
Who knows?
We're just sailin' on the wind and
the waves, going where they take us.
[ZORO grunts]
Don't you find it dumb that someone
trying to be King of the Pirates
doesn't have a single
navigational skill?!
Not really...
I just drift around...
What about you, aren't you some
famous bounty hunter who sailed the seas?
I don't have any recollection
of ever calling myself a bounty hunter.
[ZORO sighs]
I set out onto the open sea
in search of just one man,
but then I couldn't
get back to my village.
By that point, I had no choice but to
go after pirate ships to earn a living.
Oh, I see. So you're just lost.
Hey, don't put it like that!
[LUFFY grunts]
[HENCHMAN A chuckles]
Another big haul today!
That's two in a row!
[HENCHMAN B]
All of this should keep Buggy
from getting too mad at us.
[HENCHMAN C]
Hey..
What's with that boat out there?
[HENCHMEN]
Huh?
We should check it out.
Oh... It's a lady.
[HENCHMAN A chuckles]
Hey, wake up little girl.
Uh.
Please tell me I'm not
dreaming this time...
Finding help out here
in the middle of nowhere...
If you're real, then please,
could you get me some water?
I'm so thirsty...
I'll give you as much jewelry
and valuables as you like,
if you could just
give me one little drink.
No sweat. We'll help ya.
But not until we see what kinda
treasure you're holding on to.
[HENCHMAN B]
Yeah, don't mind us.
[HENCHMAN C chuckling]
We'll just be a minute.
[GIRL groans]
[HENCHMAN A]
Can't get the damn thing open!
Uh. Hold up, here we go.
[HENCHMEN scream]
[GIRL laughing]
If you want, you can
keep the whole thing!
It's not my style.
[energetic music]
[HENCHMEN scream]
But that's our boat!
You tricked us!
From the look of those clouds moving in
from the south, I'd say a cold front's coming.
So you can probably expect strong winds
and squalls any time now, really.
Also, in that small boat,
you run a bit of a chance of capsizing.
[HENCHMEN gasp]
[HENCHMEN screaming]
[GIRL]
Bingo!
See ya!
I'll just take whatever
treasure you guys got here!
[HENCHMAN A]
Get back here, you bitch!
[HENCHMAN B gurgling]
We'll get you for this!
[ZORO]
Uh. I am so hungry. It's killing me!
[LUFFY]
Hm?
[ZORO]
Hey, look, a bird.
I know! Let's eat it!
Huh? How do we catch it?
[LUFFY]
Leave that to me!
Gum-Gum...
Rocket!
Makes sense...
[LUFFY yelps]
[ZORO]
Hm?
[LUFFY groaning]
[energetic music]
[LUFFY screaming]
Help me!
You moron! What the
hell's going on now?!
[HENCHMAN A gasps]
Hey, you there! Stop!
Please! Men overboard!
Stop! Men overboard!
I can't believe I find
ship-wreckers at a time like this!
I can't stop, you're just
gonna have to jump in!
[HENCHMEN]
What?!
[HENCHMEN screaming]
I'm actually impressed
you made it onboard.
[HENCHMEN]
Are you trying to kill us?!
[HENCHMAN A]
Stop the boat now!
The three of us are members
of Buggy the Clown's pirate crew.
This boat is ours now!
Huh?
[HENCHMAN A laughing]
[HENCHMAN B & C laughing]
I'm sorry...
We had no idea you were the
famous Pirate Hunter Zoro! [chuckle]
[HENCHMEN]
Please forgive us!
[ZORO]
Thanks to you three idiots,
I lost sight of my friend.
So just keep paddling.
[HENCHMEN]
Yes, sir!
Knowing Luffy...
he'll probably pull off
something once he spots land.
[HENCHMAN B]
So, any ideas about what we do now?
[HENCHMAN C]
Good question.
If Captain Buggy finds out a girl stole
our boat and our treasure, we're history.
[HENCHMAN A]
I know...
[ZORO]
Huh? So who is this Buggy guy?
[HENCHMAN A]
Uh... You've never heard
of Buggy the Clown?!
[ZORO]
Nope.
He's the ruthless captain
of our pirate ship.
And he's eaten one of the Devil Fruits!
But above everything else,
he is a one truly terrifying man.
[GIRL]
Yes, I've finally got it!
Hey girl, get back here!
You better give us
that map back or else!
[HENCHMAN X] We just stole
that chart of the Grand Line!
It belongs to us!
Dammit!
If we don't get that thing back,
then we're as good as dead!
We'll be killed by one of
the Captain's cannonballs!
[HENCHMAN X]
Captain Buggy!
I've spotted something high
in the sky above the port.
[BUGGY]
Well, shoot it down!
What's that?
What... was that?!
What the hell...?
A guy fell from the sky.
[LUFFY]
Dammit...
Why were there
cannonballs flying at me?
[LUFFY]
At least I'm safe now.
And...
what just happened to me
was awesome.
Geez...
[LUFFY]
I'm so hungry.
Oh, hey, boss!
Thanks for coming to save me!
Huh?
Who're you?
[GIRL]
They're all yours now, boss.
Have fun!
[HENCHMAN X]
Hey! That girl's getting away!
[HENCHMAN X] That's okay.
We've got her boss now.
[HENCHMAN X]
You're in trouble, kid.
You should have let
your crony fend for herself.
You guys know of anywhere
good to eat around here?
Food's the least of
your worries now!
[gasps]
You better keep your
hands off my hat!
[BOTH]
You bastard!
I wonder if they've
killed that poor guy yet.
[LUFFY]
Gum-Gum Pistol!
[GIRL]
Wow.
You're really strong!
Huh?
Even though both of them had sabers,
you beat them barehanded.
[LUFFY]
Hey! You're the girl who set me up.
Who are you?
I'm a talented thief
who steals strictly from pirates.
The name's Nami.
Hey... Wanna team up with me?
Um, thanks anyway, lady,
but I think I'll pass.
[NAMI stammers]
Hold on...!
[NAMI]
At least think about it first.
[BUGGY]
You're telling me they
still haven't caught the thief?
[HENCHMAN X]
Uh...
Not yet...
But...
But they should be in pursuit...
right now, Captain... Sir.
Now explain to me, how in the world did she
manage to get her hands on that chart, huh?!
[whimpering]
If we're preparing to enter
the Grand Line, and go on a rampage,
then why wasn't the chart
properly guarded?!
I-I don't know, sir...
The map was just sitting out,
plain as the nose on your face.
[BUGGY snorts]
What did you say?!
I-I mean it was easy for
her to find and take it!
[BUGGY]
Did you say something
about my nose?!
So!
Are you trying to tell me
you find my nose funny?
Is my nose amusing?
No, sir, you've misunderstood!
Oh, no, you were quite clear!
[HENCHMAN X whimpering]
[HENCHMAN X]
Help me...
This isn't good...
He's... gonna use the devil fruit power!
[BUGGY growls] [whimpering]
Tell me, who am I?!
[HENCHMAN X choking]
Captain...
Buggy...
And what happens
if someone defies me?
Flashy... death... awaits... them...
Please... forgive me!
[BUGGY]
Quit your groveling.
I'll overlook your slip-up
and forgive you this time.
But you better get that chart back.
Don't screw up again... Or else.
[HENCHMEN]
Yes, Captain Buggy!
Yum.
So, do you live in this
big house all by yourself?
This isn't my house, I'm just
staying here for the time being.
Everyone's left this town
because of Captain Buggy.
[LUFFY]
So you're just a petty thief.
[NAMI]
How rude!
I only steal from people
who deserve it: pirates.
So don't compare me
to some scumbag, petty thief.
A thief's a thief,
as far as I'm concerned.
My goal is to earn a hundred million berries,
no matter how hard it is, or how long it takes.
[LUFFY]
Hm.
What do you need
so many berries for anyway?
[NAMI]
It's a secret.
But with this chart of the Grand Line...
the hundred million is
now a definite possibility.
A chart.
So you must be a navigator.
I'm the most skilled navigator
you're ever likely to meet.
Oh, wow. That's perfect!
Then how about you join my crew?
I've been looking to recruit a navigator.
Really?
Sure!
You can be our newest crew member!
No!
I suppose this means you're a pirate.
Yeah.
I made a solemn promise.
I promised the guy who gave me
this hat that I'd form a crew,
and become the greatest pirate ever.
There's nothing in this world
that I despise more than pirates!
I only like money and tangerines!
[LUFFY]
Come on.
Be our navigator.
I said no!
Your loss.
[HENCHMAN X]
Did you find her or what?!
No! I can't find her anywhere!
[HENCHMAN X]
Where could she be hiding?
I don't know, but we're gonna be
in big trouble if we don't get that chart back.
[NAMI]
I gotta do something about them.
[chuckles]
I guess I might consider joining you,
but only if you'll agree to certain conditions.
[LUFFY]
Really? I'll do anything!
Well then, I want you to come with me
to pay a little visit to Buggy the Pirate.
But first...
Why did you have to tie me up?
The rope's just for appearances.
[LUFFY chuckles]
Well, okay then...
I've been looking forward to meeting
some other pirates, so let's get going.
Just hold your horses!
What's the big rush?
[BUGGY]
What?!
Are you telling me
the thief got away?!
[HENCHMEN whimpering]
[ALL]
Please forgive us, Captain Buggy!
I've never seen a more
pathetic group than you three!
Time to die!
[ALL scream]
Captain Buggy, I have news!
[BUGGY]
Ugh. What is it?!
The girl who stole our chart is back,
and with a prisoner.
[BUGGY]
What?!
[HENCHMAN X]
It's her!
That's the sneaky thief
who stole the chart!
[NAMI]
I've captured the thief,
Captain Buggy the Clown.
And here's your chart back!
Not that I don't appreciate it.
But... why the sudden
change of heart, little girl?
I had another fight with my boss,
and I just can't take it anymore!
So I thought I'd see
if I could join your crew!
You're fed up, huh?
I must admit, you're an amusing girl.
I like you! Of course
you can join my crew!
[NAMI]
I've successfully infiltrated them!
Pirates are so dumb
and easy to manipulate!
Hey, guys, why am I in a cage?
It's a great day to be a pirate.
Girl, what do you call yourself?
I'm Nami.
Ha-ha!
Then let's have a welcome party
for our new friend Nami.
Let's celebrate!
[HENCHMEN cheering]
[HENCHMEN chattering]
What's wrong?
We're throwing this party
in your honor, so eat up.
Thanks for the party, Captain Buggy.
[NAMI]
I'll just keep my eyes peeled
for a chance to take back that chart.
Maybe I'll swipe all of Buggy's
treasure, too, while I'm at it.
Dammit!
This is such a flashy party.
Now listen up!
Men, it's time
to prepare the Buggy Ball!
[HENCHMAN X]
All set, captain.
Wh-What are you
doing with that thing?
Just observe... the awesome
might of the Buggy Ball.
Light it.
That was one heck of an explosion.
It looked like it was one of
the Captain's beloved Buggy Balls.
Buggy Balls?
That was flashy.
With these Buggy Balls
and my devil fruit powers,
I should have no problem
conquering the Grand Line.
Right, Nami?
Right! Yes, of course!
[LUFFY]
Huh?
– [NAMI gasps]
– [BUGGY] Huh?
But it's my destiny to
conquer the Grand Line.
[growls]
And then I'm gonna become
King of the Pirates!
Shut up, idiot!
[BUGGY]
I can see why
you're sick of him, Nami.
Yeah, I know.
He never takes anything seriously,
thinks that life's a big game.
He acts like a little kid.
– [NAMI laughs]
– [BUGGY] I see...
[BUGGY]
Then how about I give you a Buggy
Ball to blow away your old boss?
Huh?
It'll be a great opportunity for you to prove
your loyalty to me, your new captain.
Men!
That's all right Captain, we don't have to finish him off quite yet.
Let's get back to the welcoming
party and just have more fun.
This is my idea of having more fun.
[HENCHMEN]
– Fire! Fire! Fire!
Fire! Fire! Fire! Fire!
Fire! Fire! Fire! Fire! Fire! Fire!
[NAMI]
If I don't shoot, I'll be killed.
But if I do shoot, then
I'm no better than these pirates...
Now!
Light the fuse, Nami!
Fire
More fire
omg more fire
[LUFFY]
What's the matter?
Your hands are shaking.
[LUFFY]
That's what happens
when you take on pirates
with half‐assed resolve.
To kill someone
like it's nothing?
Is that a pirate's resolve?
[LUFFY]
No!
You gotta be willing
to risk your own life.
[HENCHMEN]
Fire! Fire! Fire!
[NAMI gasps]
Here, new chick.
Quit bein' sucha tease.
Let me show you how
to light the cannon.
My mistake... Sorry.
[BUGGY growls]
Nami!
What's the meaning
of this outrage?!
[NAMI]
I'm sorry.
What's wrong?! Just
shoot him already!
[HENCHMAN X chuckles]
Hey, wake up little girl.
[GIRL]
Uh.
Please tell me I'm not
dreaming this time...
finding help out here
in the middle of nowhere...
If you're real, then please,
could you get me some water?
I'm so thirsty.
I'll give you as much jewelry
and valuables as you like,
Pirates took the life of
a person very dear to me.
I'll never be one of them.
Oh, I see.
[LUFFY yelps]
Nami! The fuse!
[gasps]
So you think pirates
are just inhuman filth,
is that right?
Get her, men!
[HENCHMEN yelling]
Flashy... death...
awaits... them...
Water, water,
water, water, water!
[NAMI grunts]
Whoa!
Watch out!
– [HENCHMEN yelling]
– [NAMI gasps]
[ZORO]
Hey now.
[laughs]
Zoro!
[NAMI]
Huh?
[ZORO]
You hurt?
[NAMI]
Uh, no, I'm fine, I think.
[LUFFY]
Whew, what a relief!
I'm glad you found us.
Now hurry up and come
get me out of here.
[ZORO] How do keep getting
yourself into these situations?
First a bird flies off with you,
and now I find you
trapped in a cage.
[LUFFY] It's an
interesting story, actually.
That's...
Yeah... That little brat
just called him Zoro.
[NAMI]
The crew he mentioned earlier...
was the Pirate Hunter Zoro?
[LUFFY]
Hm?
[ZORO]
Hey, look, a bird.
[NAMI]
The crew he mentioned earlier...
was the Pirate Hunter Zoro?
What's going on here?
[BUGGY]
So you're Zoro?
[NAMI gasps]
[BUGGY]
If you're here for my head,
you've got quite a
struggle before you.
Now I'm really pissed off!
Alright, Prepare all the
remaining Special Buggy Balls.
But I'm interested, though.
Killing you would
bolster my reputation.
If you try...
you'll die.
Oh. Is that so?
I tried to warn you,
but oh well...
[HENCHMAN X]
You can do it, Buggy!
[HENCHMEN cheering]
[HENCHMEN]
Buggy! Buggy! Buggy!
[snickers]
[BUGGY yelling, laughing]
[BUGGY]
Die flashily!
If you'll accept, I'll
even pay you to stop this.
That wasn't much of
a fight, now was it?
Oh, wow!
He's weak! Way to go, Zoro!
Hey, why are they laughing?
Their captain is lying
dead on the ground
and yet they're still laughing?
What's going on?
[ZORO]
Fellas.
What do you find so damn funny?
– [thud]
– [ZORO grunts]
[ZORO groans]
[ZORO screams]
[LUFFY]
Stupid, stupid, stupid, dog!
Give it back. That's not food!
Give me my key!
Give it, give it, give it, give
it, give it, give it, give it!
[ZORO gasps]
[BUGGY]
The Chop‐Chop Fruit.
I'm a Chop‐Chop person,
[laughing]
His limbs... reattach?
And I always thought that the
devil fruits were just a story
that Pirates told.
So he's a Chop‐Chop man?
That's pretty freaky.
I didn't hit any vital organs,
but that's a serious
wound you have there.
So I'm guessing...
but that's a serious
wound you have there.
So I'm guessing...
Buggy Balls?
[NAMI]
Oh, crap!
The tables have turned.
If we don't do something quick,
[groaning]
[HENCHMEN]
Buggy! Buggy! Buggy!
[snickers]
[BUGGY yelling, laughing]
[BUGGY]
Die flashily!
[NAMI whimpers]
[HENCHMEN gasp]
Shut up, idiot!
[laughing]
[BUGGY] I can see why
you're sick of him, Nami.
What's that...
you...
[HENCHMAN X] So, any ideas
about what we do now?
Luffy!
I'm here to kick your ass, just
like I promised I would, Buggy!
[BUGGY laughing]
You kick my ass?
You've got a lot of nerve, kid.
No, I'm afraid all three of you
are going to die here
today, by my own hand.
So if you're going to
do any ass kicking,
you better do it soon.
[BUGGY laughing]
[NAMI gasps]
[LUFFY laughing]
[LUFFY]
I refuse to die!
Zoro! Get up!
What?!
You better have a really good
plan or else we're all dead.
I gotcha.
[ZORO] You're a rubber guy.
How human do you think that is?
[GIRL]
Nothing makes sense anymore.
A rubber guy,
This is why I hate pirates.
[BUGGY]
Impudent fool! Time to die!
[BUGGY] Your Three‐Sword
Style has no effect on me.
[GIRL panting]
[GIRL]
Yes, I've finally got it!
Hey girl, get back here!
I already told you I'm‐‐
– [BUGGY screams]
– [HENCHMEN gasp]
Light it.
[chuckles]
[yelps]
That was one heck
of an explosion.
It looked like it was one of the
Captain's beloved Buggy Balls.
Buggy Balls?
[NAMI]
At least think about it first.
[stomach rumbling]
I just remembered...
Done in by my own balls!
[laughing]
[BUGGY] I can't believe
you just did that,
you ungrateful little girl!
Wait!
N‐N‐No!
Stop!
Stop it now!
♪As a kid, I never stopped
Searching for a great treasure
I had a map in my mind
You okay, Zoro?
How bad are you injured.
Just shut up and don't
worry about how I'm doing.
I need to concentrate if
I'm gonna get us outta this.
Who is... this guy?
Hey, Luffy, who's this?
Who's the girl?
Oh, right. She's
our new navigator.
I'm not so sure about that.
Who are you guys, anyway?
[ZORO]
Move...[grunts]
You're in the way.
I guess even a lowly pirate...
...can still rescue his friend.
Nami, a Pirate Thief
Buggy "the Clown"
Pirate Captain
m 501.75 837 l 949.5 837 949.5 945 501.75 945
Rubber Person