Your media player does not support the subtitle format used in this episode.
Subtitles will likely not function properly.
Please use one of the recommended video players, preferably mpv:
https://mpv.io
Your media player does not support the subtitle format used in this episode.
Subtitles will likely not function properly.
Please use one of the recommended video players, preferably mpv:
https://mpv.io
Ten years ago, in the East Blue...
there was a little hamlet known as
Windmill Village, where people lived peacefully.
Not far from there was Mt. Colubo,
where none dared set foot.
There, it was survival of the fittest.
As for the weak, death was all but certain.
Grandpa, I'm telling you...
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates...
What's this King of the Pirates crap?!
L-Let me go!
First you eat that devil fruit,
and now you're spouting nonsense!
Luffy! Both you and Ace
are gonna be strapping Marines!
Ow, ow, ow, dammit!
Why does this hurt when my body is rubber?!
Let me go, Grandpa!
Leaving you in Windmill Village was a mistake!
It just had to be pirates!
What is this place?
Stop that! Say your prayers, whoever you are!
It's me.
M-Mr. Garp!
You seem well.
This isn't funny! Please,
you can't do this to me!
That Ace kid is ten years old now!
Oh, already? How is he?
It's not funny!
We can't handle him anymore!
You have to take him back!
Putting that aside...
Don't put it aside!
Will you pipe down, kid?!
I'd like you to look after him, too.
Hey, Luffy. Say hi.
Sup?
Who's the kid?
He's my grandson.
Wha...?
– What?!
Another one?!
He's Garp's... I mean, Mr. Garp's grandson?!
– We can't!
All right! Here are your choices:
Spend the rest of your life
in a cell, or raise this kid.
I've turned a blind eye to
who-knows-how-many of your crimes.
– No fair!
Well, I don't wanna get arrested but...
Sometimes I feel like prison might
actually be better than raising Ace.
And now you're saddling
us with your grandson?
I bet this kid's some kind of monster too.
What a crummy shack!
I'll knock you into next week!
He ignored me!
– Boss!
Are you alright?!
What the...? Ugh! It's spit! Gross!
Who's there?!
Hey, you!
Say you're sorry! That was gross!
Hm? Ace!
Oh! Are you back, Ace?!
Hey! Say sorry!
Luffy, this is Ace.
He's three years older than you.
Starting today, you'll be living together.
– What?!
It's not decided yet!
Be nice!
It is decided?!
Is there a problem?
– Happy to have him!
It's your turn to wash dishes!
More!
Gimme some more, pops!
I'll have you know I'm a woman!
Do you even know where you are now?!
No.
Then I'll tell you.
You're in the den of the Dadan Family,
the mountain bandits of Mt. Colubo!
Mountain bandits? I hate mountain bandits!
Shut it, you brat! We're the ones
who got stuck with a little snot like you!
If you don't like it here, fine!
Get lost and die like a dog!
Take it easy, Boss.
I wanna eat more...
Gimme some of that meat too.
All this meat is from a bison
that Ace took down for us.
He gave us a cut of the haul
so that everyone can eat.
Mountain bandits have it tough.
Starting tomorrow,
I'm gonna work your butt off!
Cleaning, laundry,
polishing shoes and weapons,
burglary, robbery, fraud, and murder!
And remember, you can never
tell Garp what we make you do!
You get one bowl of rice
and one glass of water each day!
That's all I can guarantee you.
You've gotta get everything else
on your own and take care of yourself.
Okay!
"Okay"?! Just like that?! No waterworks?!
This one time, Grandpa threw me into a jungle!
This is a forest, so there's plenty of water to drink
and frogs, snakes and mushrooms to eat!
Plus, I'm gonna be a pirate someday...
so I have to take care of myself!
– Boss!
– Are you alright?!
What are you doing?!
– Heave ho!
Where's he headed?
Where are you going?!
Did you just say "pirate"?
He ignored me!
Hey!
See? I knew he'd be a handful! That's why
I didn't wanna take care of Garp's grandson!
Take it easy, Boss.
Hey!
Wait for me!
My name's Luffy! I'm not mad
about you spitting on me anymore!
Why are you laughing?!
He only got some booze on me.
It's nothing worth getting mad over.
It's nothing worth getting
mad over! Let's be friends!
Are you going somewhere?!
It's a dead end!
Hey! Ace is back!
– Food's here!
Ace, are you by yourself?
Hey, where's Luffy?
I thought he went with you.
Dunno.
Get it together, Boss!
What'd you say?!
I'm saying it's really bad that
we lost him on the first day!
Leave me alone! If he dies, he dies!
I've already given up on Ace, too!
Even if he winds up dead somewhere,
all I have to do is tell Garp it was an accident.
As they say, "The devil's children
have the devil's luck."
He's demon spawn!
If the government finds out that he's here,
what do you think they'd do to us?!
Take it easy, Boss.
You're drinking too much!
One week later...
Boss! Boss Dadan!
Who– Huh?!
Who is it...? Huh?!
It's you!
Luffy came back!
Why, you...!
You survived, you little sh–
Take it easy, Boss.
Where were you?!
Take it easy! Where were you
and what were you doing?
Wolves were chasing me through the ravine.
What were you doing in the ravine?!
Anyway, good thing you're okay.
Yeah, it's good.
Like hell it's good!
The pest came back!
Just go to bed already! I'll start
working you like a dog tomorrow!
Already?!
Morning!
Where you off to today, Ace?
Take me with you! Let's be friends!
Wait up!
Boss! He's chasing after Ace again!
Hey! You've got chores to do!
No way!
You're out of control, you little turd!
Take it eas–
Bring him back right now!
Yes, ma'am.
Hey!
Even though he always lost track of Ace....
he kept chasing him day after day.
Ace!
For one month...
For two months...
Ace!
No matter the rain...
No matter the wind...
Ace!
Luffy was relentless in his pursuit of Ace.
Ace! Hey!
I can't believe he followed me
all the way here. He's so persistent.
Oh, crap!
Damn! I lost him again! Ace sure is quick!
That you, Ace?!
That's the beast of Mt. Colubo!
No one can beat that thing!
Why won't he run?! It's gonna eat him!
M-My legs w-won't move!
Tch! That twerp!
After three months of cuts,
bruises, and endless pursuit...
It's the edge of the forest.
Whoa! What is this place?!
North of Mt. Colubo, where the Dadan
Family resides, lies a neglected place.
Smoke endlessly emanates from
heaps of discarded trash.
Unwanted things accumulate here.
Its inhabitants are outlaws,
shunned by mainstream society.
Naturally, the law holds no sway here.
Without so much as a doctor,
the area teems with crime and disease.
This is the Gray Terminal.
Come on out, treasure...
Isn't there anything worth selling around here?
I got something!
They're mine!
No, they're mine!
Lay off! I found them!
Hands off the goods, you vultures!
I'm gonna sell them in town!
Like hell you will!
Get back here!
Damn you!
Drop 'em!
If you'd just handed 'em over,
I wouldn't have needed to sock you!
Nice going!
Why, you...! Are you kidding me?!
Thief!
Move it, kid!
Hurry it up! Move or I'll...
He went that way!
Sabo! Sabo, are you there?
Oh, Ace!
Sorry I'm late.
You sure are!
I already finished a job in town.
Oh, yeah? Truth is, so did I.
– Same time!
Whoa! That's a lot...! A lot more than I made!
What a haul! How'd you pull it off?!
I stole it from some thugs near the Great Gate.
Damn! You win again!
It doesn't matter who wins, does it?
This pirate fund is for the both of us.
It's been five years
since we started saving, huh?
We've worked hard.
We sure have!
To leave the East Blue and sail into a world
these island hicks couldn't even dream of...
it just gets me so pumped!
Hurry and close the lid.
You never know who's watching.
How much do you think
we'll need for a pirate ship?
Who knows? Hundreds of thousands,
or maybe even millions...
We'll get there one day.
"A pirate ship"?!
Are you guys gonna be pirates?!
I'm gonna be one too!
Hey!
– Be quiet!
Ace! This is where you've
been going every day?!
Shut up.
So this is that Luffy kid you told me about.
Oh, you told him about me?!
I complained about how persistent you are.
And about how airheaded you seem!
I see!
Doesn't he get that we're insulting him?
He finally made it all the way here.
I even made sure to avoid the main pathways.
Are you Ace's friend?! Be my friend, too!
Shut up! We don't even know each other!
Then, what's your name?
Sa–
I'm not telling!
This is why I told you to live here with me!
Your daily round trip "training" through
the mountains was a bad idea after all!
What do we do?
Now he knows our secret.
He'll spill the beans if we don't do something.
We gotta kill him.
Alright, let's do it.
Wha...?!
What?!
Don't kill me! Someone save me!
I don't wanna die!
You idiot! Be quiet!
Sabo! Hurry and do it!
Why me?! You do it!
I've never killed anyone before!
Neither have I! I don't know how to do it!
Please don't throw me into water!
Right! The river!
Why'd he give that away?!
'Cause he's a moron!
Somebody help me!
– Shut up!
I don't wanna die! No!
There's a voice coming from the forest!
A kid's voice!
Oh, no! Someone's coming!
Let's just untie him!
If we don't clear out, they'll find our treasure!
Those brats, Ace and Sabo,
are infamous around these parts.
You're absolutely certain
it was Ace who swiped the cash, right?
Yeah... It's embarrassing, but we got sloppy.
I can't believe that kid...
laying his hands on our crew's loot!
If Captain Bluejam hears
about this, we're all dead!
Damn it! Those thugs were Bluejam's lackeys?
Thugs? You mean you got
that money from those guys?
We've got some dangerous
money on our hands...
He has a real sword...
Porchemy is one of Bluejam's goons.
He's crazy. Have you heard?
When he beats someone, he scalps them alive!
Let's hope they just move along...
Huh? Where'd he go?
Let go of me! What are you doing?
– How'd he get caught?!
Who's this little shit?
Help me!
Ace!
Help me, Ace!
You dumbass...!
Shouting my name like that...!
Ace! Ace! Ace!
Did you just say "Ace"?
Yeah, so?!
Do you know Ace?
He's my friend!
Oh, but he was going to kill me just now.
Just. Stop. Talking.
I need to ask...
Earlier today, Ace stole
some of our money and ran off.
You wouldn't happen to know
where he put it, would you?
Oh, crap! They're gonna take our treasure!
That airhead better not blab...
– What?!
Huh?!
I-I don't know...
What a terrible liar!
All right, all right. If you
don't know, then that's that.
I'll help jog your memory, so don't worry!
What the hell?! Let me go!
Where are you taking me?!
Damn it! Idiot! Let go of me!
You bastard!
What do we do?
"What do we do?" Well...
Let me go!
I'm not telling you anything!
You little shit!
I tried to tell you, but I'm all rubbery
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit!
Quiet!
A devil fruit, huh?
Yeah, you're the genuine article.
Get my gloves.
Wha...?! Y-Yes, sir!
Hurry up! Hurry up! We're screwed
if Porchemy and his goons come back!
We've gotta move the treasure fast!
It's only a matter of time before
that Luffy kid rats us out!
If they find this, they won't just
take back what we stole from them,
but the entire pirate fund
from over the past five years!
Listen, you little shit.
The cash that your friend Ace stole
was important to our pirate crew...
and you know where it is!
So, you will tell me.
I won't!
That's gotta hurt!
You shouldn't piss off a pirate!
Our captain, Bluejam, is a brutal monster!
That hurt! I'm scared!
Somebody save me!
You guys, find Ace and Sabo!
Don't just stand there twiddling your thumbs!
– Yes, sir!
You're asking about Ace and Sabo?
You must be delinquents from the city.
You're better off not getting
involved with those two.
Don't underestimate 'em
just 'cause they're puny.
Those mad dogs turn tigers into mincemeat!
Ace and Sabo, huh? Haven't seen 'em...
But more importantly, fellas...
why don't you hand over your valuables?
W-We'd rather not!
Let's go look somewhere else!
It's almost nighttime...
Alright! All done!
We moved all the treasure!
Ace!
Sabo, what's wrong?
Were they looting our old hideout?
No, they never showed.
And I bet they won't!
Meaning...?
That Luffy kid...
still hasn't told them a thing!
He's definitely being tortured.
He was such an idiot crybaby that
I thought for sure he'd tell them!
I don't get it!
At this rate, he'll...
They're late...
Who was in charge today?
It was Porchemy, Captain Bluejam.
The sun's already setting.
There's no way it takes this long
to cash in the goods.
You don't think he'd run away with the money, do you?
No, he'd never...!
He wouldn't risk his life to pull a stunt like that.
You're right.
Spit it out already...!
Ah... P-P-Porchemy...!
It's no use!
He's too worn out to even scream now!
He probably won't tell us anything,
and, to be honest, this is
so brutal I can barely watch!
Let's just let him go!
If you have the time to worry about the kid,
then go find Ace and Sabo!
We're the ones who'll get killed!
Don't you get it?!
The scheduled drop-off with
Captain Bluejam is long overdue!
Poor kiddo...
Should we get the town sheriff involved?
It won't do any good.
The country's laws don't extend to this area.
Besides, that guy is on Bluejam's crew.
They pay off the nobles!
Whatever crimes they commit in this country
—even murder—will just be overlooked!
No matter how many corpses pile up
around here, nobody pays any mind!
Just tell me!
I won't!
You little shit! You're putting too
much effort into keeping this secret!
Spit it out!
I won't.
I won't!
Fine. Enough.
Die.
Stop!                                     Stop!
Outta my way!
That's the kid, Porchemy!
He's the one who stole our money, dammit!
What?
A-Ace!
You saved us time by coming here yourselves!
We were having a hard time
making your friend talk.
Ace!
L-Let me go!
Sabo!
– Porchemy!
Ace! Sabo!
That kinda hurt, y'know? Hey...!
Do you know what happens
when you mess with grown-ups?!
I'm the one you're going to fight!
Sabo! Grab the kid!
Ace!
He has a sword! Be careful!
Oh, my knife!
Porchemy, that kid...!
Let's go, Ace!
You go on ahead!
You're crazy! Hurry up!
When I face someone...
I never run!
What'd you say?! You little shit!
Don't do it! He's not like the thugs in the city!
Your friend gets it!
Now... playtime is over.
It's our money after all,
so give it back nice and easy, kid!
You probably stole it on impulse, right?
Just give the money back before you regret it.
We can put that money
to better use than you!
Wha...?
What the hell did you say?!
Wait here a minute!
Enough of your crap!
If I lose to a couple of kids,
I may as well quit being a pirate!
– Then you're gonna quit!
You're all dead!
I heard the whole story, Porchemy...
How pathetic.
You seriously let a couple of kids beat you?
I'm sorry, Captain Bluejam... The money is–
Don't look at me! You're a disgrace!
That's a real bad habit, Ace!
When faced with a real pirate, it's best to run!
Why do you have such a death wish?
It's just not the same.
I liked the last one better.
We really stepped in it this time...
The Bluejam crew isn't going to let this slide.
They'll come for us.
That was so scary!
I thought I was gonna die!
You're so annoying! Shut up!
Stop crying already!
I really can't stand cowards and crybabies!
Th-Thank you!
You...
You saved me!
You...!
Whoa, let him show some gratitude.
Why didn't you just
tell them what you knew?!
They'd even kill women
and children without hesitation!
I thought if I said anything...
you wouldn't be my friend.
It's better than dying, isn't it?
Why are you so obsessed
with being my friend?!
Because...
Haven't I been giving you a hard time?
Why would you follow me this far?
Because...
Because I don't have anyone else!
I can't go back to Windmill Village
and I hate mountain bandits!
If I didn't follow you, I'd be all alone!
Being lonely is more painful than getting hurt!
Where are your parents?
Grandpa is all I have.
So you feel better when I'm around?
Uh-huh.
You need me?
"What if Gold Roger had a child?"
We definitely don't need a kid like that around!
Demon spawn like that doesn't
even deserve to be alive!
Do you want me...
to live?
Of course I do!
Okay...
but I hate spoiled brats like you.
I'm not a spoiled brat! I'm tough!
Tough?! You're not tough at all!
Men aren't supposed to cry!
Have you ever been hit
with spikes? I'm only seven!
When I'm ten like you,
I'll be super strong and never ever cry!
I never cried when I was seven,
you dork! Don't compare us!
I'm gonna be stronger than anyone!
I promised Shanks that
I'd become a great pirate!
A pirate? You?
Yes!
– No way!
– Yes way!
Okay, that's enough!
Hey, by the way, I have a little problem.
What? A problem?
Mm-hmm...
I've been living in this forest, but it's
too close to that hideout in Pirate Bay.
What if they attack me when I'm
exhausted and fast asleep?
That's why I need your help.
How did they get hurt?
They're all bandaged up!
Hey, that's...
Whoa! Boss! Boss! We have a problem!
Huh? It's too early to "have a problem"...
Whoa! What's going on here?!
One, two...
Huh?
Ace! Luffy! Who is that?!
Who is who?
Why is there one more kid?!
Who the hell are you?!
Are you talking about me?
I'm Sabo! Hey, you must be Dadan!
Sabo? I've heard your name before!
Oh, yeah? That makes it easier!
Thank you for taking me in!
I heard you're a shitty a brat just like them!
Well, sure! And I heard that you're
a no-good, annoying old hag!
Ace! Luffy! Sabo!
I'm giving you three a place to stay,
so get to work already!
Thank you, Dadan!
After being forced to leave the Gray Terminal,
Ace's best friend Sabo moved in.
Ace, Sabo, and Luffy...
The trio soon began to spend their time
fighting wildlife in the mountains and jungle.
They also clashed with hooligans
from the city and pirates at the bay.
Eventually, their notoriety spread
even to the heart of the kingdom!
Monkey D. Garp
(10 Years Ago)
Monkey D. Luffy
Curly Dadan
Dogra
Mountain Bandit
Magra
Portgas D. Ace
(10 Years Ago)
One Week Later...
Sabo (Age 10)
(A Boy Living in the Gray Terminal)
Porchemy
Bluejam Pirates
Pirate Bay
Gray Terminal
Captain Bluejam
Bluejam Pirates