All aboard!
Is that...
That's Princess Vivi!
Have a nice trip!
Princess Vivi!
Your Highness!
Hey, Koza.
Vivi-chan looked very excited.
I guess her pirate spirit is back.
Just when I was thinking
she had become more like a princess.
Yes, this is Hina. We just left Arabasta.
We'll get the Nefertari family to Mary Geoise safely.
Mistress Hina, accept these flowers!
I picked them for you!
I don't want them.
Jango! Fullbody!
Get to your positions now!
Yes, ma'am!
Princess Vivi! Princess Vivi!
It's dangerous, Your Highness!
Please come down from there this instant!
Princess Vivi!
What a nice sea breeze...
What would you do if a strange bird comes and grabs you?!
And what if there's a sniper targeting you,
or if a meteor falls from the sky?!
You worry too much.
Her Highness used to be a pirate, after all.
What's wrong with you, Pell?!
The Navy is watching us!
Don't push yourself, Your Majesty.
If you're not feeling well,
we'll head back right away.
No, I'm fine.
Ever since I met Nico Robin,
I've wanted to ask the World Government something.
All I wanted was to know the history...
There are too many enemies in the way of my dream...
About the poneglyphs?
I'm determined to attend this year's Reverie!
If possible, I wish to learn
what it was the Nefertari kings of the past did to the world!
Oh, no! Oh, no!
Oh, no! Oh, no! Oh–
Hey! Behave yourself, Your Highness!
Father dearest, how are you?
Not well.
I might not live much longer...
If only my daughter would find a husband before it's too late.
That's not fair!
You're using your illness against me again!
We've got tons of pictures of potential suitors!
Throw them away!
Congratulations on your enthronement, sir.
Our hotel was built exclusively for royal families
who attend the Reverie every four years.
We do hope you enjoy your stay.
It isn't not-not-so-bad.
Right, darling?
Well, it's nothing special.
All it offers is a view of the scaffold
where Gold Roger was executed.
W-Well, please do ease the fatigue of your travel here,
King Sterry.
Yeah, I will. Now be gone from my sight, trash.
Y-Y-Yes, sir!
The countries of the world are in a restless state
due to the Reverie that takes place at the center of the world,
in the Holy Land of Mariejois, every four years.
Here, at the very highest of conferences, 50 leaders will come together
to discuss and debate the world's most serious topics
and agree upon a shared direction of the future.
But due to the prudent natures of the most powerful of leaders, the meetings are not always calm.
The leader of the Happo Navy, Don Chinjao...
I mean, the new leader Sai is not back yet, is he?
Since Straw Hat and the others
took down the Donquixote Family,
our enemy can't buy weapons from them.
Thanks to that, the war is over.
It seems we will make it to the Reverie in time.
There are so many things I need to say!
I can't do it.
I'm scared.
Sir Luffy made a promise to me!
When we meet again, he's going to take me
on a walk in a real forest on the surface!
Of course, Luffy-kun will be able to take you much farther if you want!
But on this trip, we're going
straight up to Mary Geoise.
Your brothers and the Neptune Army
will be there with you, Princess Shirahoshi!
Oh goodness...
Father, what if we let Shirahoshi
skip this one, mi-re-do ?
Yeah! We got tons of signatures on the petition
that asks to relocate Fishman Island!
Ooh! Mambo!
That is like saying we don't trust humans-jamon.
What should we do?
Shirahoshi, what did you learn from the Straw Hats?
This meeting is what our mother Otohime
was looking forward to.
Come with us!
King Wapol! I have a report!
Drum, the kingdom you once ruled,
has a new name. It's the Sakura Kingdom now!
They say that Dalton will be attending the Reverie as its king.
What?! The Sakura Kingdom?!
Damn that Dalton...
I wonder what I can do to drag him down at the Reverie?!
What did you say, Dr. Kureha? Are you serious?
Why do you all look so unhappy?
I said that I'll be your ship's doctor.
Aren't ya happy?
What?! Can I come too?!
Of course, you can!
Would you like to come as my lady-in-waiting?
I'd love to! Thank you, Viola-san !
You must be excited, Rebecca!
I am!
Maybe I can wear my mother's dress!
Yes! That would be great!
King Riku! I turned down the battleship escort!
Would you like to accompany me to the Holy Land?
Why does everyone think it's going to be a vacation?
What's wrong with that?
The Reverie is like a festival!
Meanwhile, Luffy's group...
Hey... turn a bit to starboard...
Okay...
Like this?
Ah... a bit more.
Hey, hey, hey!
Put some spirit into it! Or we'll sink!
Shut up! Because you jumped off the elephant all of a sudden, we're all worn out! Idiot!
Thank you. Once again I can savor the joy of being alive...
But... I'll make you pay for it!
See... we're off course again.
Turn to port...
Okay! Leave it to me!
See?! She's full of spirit...
Wow! We really are on the water!
This big heavy boat feels like it's floating in the air!
W-Why are you here?!
Whaaat?!
Carrot?!
Carrot, why are you here?!
I decided to tag along!
Garchu !
Nami!
Chopper!
Baron Corpse!
Too hard!
I'm sorry, but we have to go back!
What?!
Don't do that! Wanda's going to be mad at me!
Do you want to be a bother to our saviors, Carrot?
I just wanted to go on an adventure at sea, along with Luffy and the others, even if it's the only chance I get.
We are infiltrating the lair of an emperor.
This is no game!
Please! I'll do anything! Just take me with you!
I won't cause any trouble! I even brought...
Look!
Lunch!
Juice!
A snack!
An extra shirt!
How long do you think that'll last?
A good half day! Isn't the sea a big place?
What?! It's going to take multiple days to get to Big Mom's territory?!
Even on a straight route?!
I can't believe the ocean is so big!
The ocean is like a wonderland!
I've never spent the night away from home!
A wonder...land, you say?
We're in the ocean.
Oh, well. You're on board now, so we'll have to deal with it!
Can you defend yourself in a fight?
Yes! Thank you! I'll be alright...
Why are you eating my carrot?!
Pat her head, Luffy!
That was close!
You almost killed me! You're strong!
It's fine, you can have the carrot.
Luffy almost lost!
Well, she is a good fighter.
Pedro-san, when did you get up there?
You really like heights.
I'm hungry. Let's eat.
Somebody, make something!
All right! I'll do it,
so just watch the waves for me, okay?
Yes, sir!
Yay!
It'll be 5,000 belly per person.
Wait! Wait! Wait! Wait! Wait! Wait! Wait!
That'll drain all of our allowances!
Then what should we do?
Either I make the food, or you do it, Brook.
You're right.
If we leave it to Luffy-san,
who knows what he'll make for us?!
I'll make something!
What?!
You can count on me!
I'll cook you a lot of delicious dishes!
Oh, no...
Oh, please don't... Hey, wait!
Food! Food! Food!
Wait! Don't do it!
Luffy! Can you even cook?!
This is quite a large headline.
"The island, for decades veiled in mystery..."
"was finally discovered."
"The Revolutionary Army's general headquarters, Baltigo..."
"The Revolutionary Army HQ has been discovered."
"is in utter ruins!"
What?!
"The Revolutionary Army HQ has been discovered."
The Revolutionary Army got defeated?!
I thought you were the son
of Dragon the Revolutionary.
Sabo!
That's my brother!
Sabo-san ?! The brother you said you met at Dressrosa?
Is he the chief of staff?! Then he's the second in command of the Revolutionary Army!
What kind of trio of brothers are you?!
Then... this Dragon guy next to him is...
Yes, that's him!
Remember what your grandpa told us two years ago!
The name of your father is...
Monkey D. Dragon. He's a revolutionary.
The commander-in-chief of the Revolutionary Army, Dragon.
That's your dad!
What?! This is my dad?!
You're just now finding that out?!
I've never seen him before!
What?! Luffy's father is
the leader of the Revolutionary Army?!
Amazing! Amazing! Garchu !
Didn't you look into him at all over the past two years?!
Normal people would be at least a little bit curious if their father was such a famous figure!
Robin even worked under him while we were separated.
I see! This is the first time I've seen him!
He doesn't really look like me.
In any case, I'm worried about Sabo!
Jeez...
Well, it is hard to empathize with a picture.
An anonymous source revealed the location of the headquarters.
But by the time the Navy and Cipher Pol arrived...
the Blackbeard Pirates had already laid the base to ruin.
Blackbeard?! Those bastards!
But... why would Blackbeard, an emperor, attack the Revolutionary Army?
Back at Dressrosa, Sabo fought that champion guy.
Maybe that had something to do with it?
Hey, Luffy!
Apparently, Blackbeard clashed briefly with Cipher Pol before fleeing.
The article doesn't say anything about any casualties.
Hey!
If your father or brother were captured or killed, it would've been the big headline.
Hey, Luffy!
So I guess they're okay for now.
Yeah! You're right!
Hey, Luffy!
What do you want?!
Thank you for cooking for us,
but is that supposed to happen?!
Huh?
Fire?!
Oh, no! I forgot to turn off the stove!
What?!
Something exploded!
Put out the fire!
Wait! A storm is coming!
What?!
What is this?! Electro?!
Hoist the sails!
The wind will rip them to shreds!
What about the fire?!
The rain will put it out!
We're lucky!
There's nothing "lucky" about it!
You help, too!
I'm half-dead!
Then... Carrot is out at sea now?!
Why didn't you tell us sooner, Bariete?
I'm sorry, Wanda!
I told Carrot that she had to
tell everyone that she was going.
But she said...
No way! If I tell anybody,
they'll try to stop me!
I see! She bribed you, didn't she?
Shock !
You caught me...
But Carrot didn't want to go behind your back, Wanda!
It's fine.
I'm just glad we know where she is.
I was more worried about her being missing.
She'll be safe if she's with Luffy's group.
My lordship, please get some rest.
I will have extra guards put in place.
I suspect that our enemy has a vivre card.
But how did they get it?!
I only hope that the card was lost with the ships Zunesha sank...
Do you think they'll come back?
We'd better be on the lookout.
Indeed.
Hurry up!
Hurry up and pull me out of here!
As we thought,
Captain Jack failed to rescue Joker!
That puts an end to our arrangement
for those artificial SMILE devil fruits!
He's a crying drunk today.
Then... we can't make any more gifters!
Joker! Oh, Joker!
How did you let yourself get beaten?!
We were going to create the greatest crew ever,
made up of just devil fruit users!
And yet...
You were taken out by a bunch of upstart brats before that dream could come true!
Poor, poor Joker! It's all because he was such a terrible weakling...
But everyone's talking about Straw Hat these days.
If you underestimate him...
If I underestimate him...
Then what?!
Who do you think I am?!
He turned into an angry drunk!
L-Lord Kaido... Please calm down!
Straw Hat Luffy! Trafalgar Law!
I know! They're from that generation, right?!
Those brats think they're something
just because they brought down a warlord!
They must be aware that they messed with my business!
Screw them!
Hey, you there!
Tell those idiots from your generation this:
"Run away now while you can.
All we've been doing is playing pirates!"
Eustass "Captain" Kid!
Oh, it's cold!
We patched up the roof!
Okay, good work.
All right! The storm has passed!
And we patched up the roof that blew off!
We kept the food I made safe, so let's eat!
Yay! Food! We're starving!
Oh, is it that good?!
My specialty curry!
Luffy, we can't eat uncooked rice!
What's that bitter purple stuff?
It's full of fish bones.
Too much jam!
There's something sticky and light blue.
What did we do to deserve this?
How could you guys be so rude
after I took the time to cook this!
Yuck!
See, we told you!
This isn't edible!
Don't flip the table over!
How dare you waste food!
Sanji-san would be mad if he heard about this!
All the food we loaded... it's gone!
Yeah, I messed up a lot, so I used all of it.
What?! That was a week's
worth of food for all of us!
I thought you were hungry!
It's not funny!
What are we supposed to do now?!
Luffy...
Hey, I'm starving...
Sanji-san ! Help us!
And so, in just the first day of Luffy's journey...
the crew was at risk of starvation.
♪ Ship! Ship! Ship! Ship! ♪
I thought this was snow, but...
It's a cotton candy flurry-soir !
That transponder snail's been ringing off the hook...
It's receiving warning signals-bon.
That means we're in
Mama's territory now-soufflé.
Does the signal extend to that spot over there?
You're a quick learner! That's Tarte 28.
It is an outpost where a platoon from
the Big Mom Pirates is standing ready-millefeuille !
If we weren't on one of Mama's ships,
they'd attack us with a rapid "boom"!
Now, have you made up your mind?
Don't be so stubborn.
Follow Germa 66's example and swear allegiance to the Big Mom Pirates-bon.
That is your father's wish-amour.
Don't talk about him!
It makes me sick to my stomach!
Our relationship has already been broken off!
I'm only going there to clear things up.
Don't try to act tough.
Mama is in a more
welcoming mood than you might think.
Of course, she knows you're
that foolish Straw Hat's comrade-s'il vous plaît.
But she admires how you were once a chef at the sea restaurant in the East Blue-bon.
Depending on your skill, she may offer you an even better position-jour.
Screw that!
Listen! The only use for these hands of mine...
is to cook food for my friends!
For that purpose, I even trained myself in hell!
I'm sure they're missing my food and crying about it right now...
How absurd!
I would never make a dish for the kind of people...
who would take out their own comrades without a second thought!
Oh, you're talking about Pekoms, huh?
He let his personal feelings interfere with his work.
Bege did the right thing.
Baron Tamago.
Vito!
We got a photo of Lady Pudding
from Whole Cake Island!
So you can prepare yourself.
They know it's hard to marry someone you've never met. How nice of them to send this.
It doesn't matter, you idiot.
I'm not getting married!
Just take a look.
Shut up! Stay away or I'll kick you to death!
Well, come on.
Cut it out...
This is your bride-to-be...
The 35th daughter of the Charlotte family.
Lady Charlotte Pudding!
Arabasta
The Kingdom of Sand
"Black Cage" Hina
Navy HQ Rear Admiral
Nefertari Vivi
Princess of Arabasta
Nefertari Cobra
King of Arabasta
Loguetown, East Blue
Sarie Nantokanette
Queen of Goa
Kano Country, West Blue
The Ryugu Kingdom
Beneath the Red Line
Shirahoshi
Princess of the Ryugu Kingdom
Ryuboshi
Prince of the Ryugu Kingdom
Manboshi
King Neptune
Ruler of the Ryugu Kingdom
Fukaboshi
Prince of the Ryugu Kingdom
The Evil Kingdom of Black Drum
South Blue
The Sakura Kingdom
The Grand Line
Dalton
King of the Sakura Kingdom
Dressrosa
The Country of Passion
The Kingdom of Prodence
Elizabello II
King of Prodence
Riku Doldo III
King of Dressrosa
Carrot
Member of the Mink Musketeers
Zou
In a Certain Country
Back on the
Thousand Sunny
A Few Days Later
on Big Mom's Ship
MUNCH!
CHOMP!
CRUNCH!