♪ Booo-il, boil, boil! ♪
♪ Boil, boil! Boil, bo-iiil! ♪
Chobro, help! It's hot!
Stop whining, you brat!
I don't eat humans, but...
minks could be edible,
so I gotta try.
Don't eat me! I'm not delicious!
Let Carrot go, Brûlée!
She's not a real rabbit!
Of course, she's not delicious!
What? Is that true?
He's right!
Then, maybe I shouldn't try.
I'm too tough and stinky and disgusting!
I'm not gonna let her go.
Keep your mouth shut, you odd reindeer.
You'll join Mama's collection
of strange beasts!
C-Collection of strange beasts?
That's right. So just sit there quietly.
Okay! We managed to get to this point.
I made sure to get tied up in Heavy Point,
so I could escape from these
chains instantly by transforming.
I'm giving Chopper trouble!
Pedro will be mad at me!
It's been at least six hours since I used Monster
Point yesterday, so that's at my disposal, too!
♪ When the delicious soup is ready, ♪
♪ dump her in! ♪
♪ Booo-il, boil, boil! ♪
♪ She's gonna be delicious! Let's try! ♪
♪ Booo-il, boil, boil! Puff, puff! ♪
Chobro!
Now's the chance!
Here it is.
Within books, you can find an infinite array of worlds.
Look. This is a super-rare, man-eating lion
with a human face.
A manticore.
It's a strange beast that
escaped from Impel Down
during Blackbeard's assault two years ago.
Loincloth, loincloth!
It moved!
And this one is my pride and joy!
Isn't it beautiful?
Well... close enough. But it's living in the book.
The animals within the books will never age.
It makes sense, right?
The contents of a book never change.
Help!
The books in this library contain
rare creatures from all over the world.
Cool!
That's what my son, Mont d'Or, is capable of.
Recently, we got a centaur from Punk Hazard,
and a griffin from the South Blue.
I even got one of these!
A long-limbed human!
Help!
Let me out!
Even a human?
Big Mom.
Since I stepped into this country,
I've seen a wide variety of races.
Of course! Because that's the kind of country
that Totto Land is supposed to be!
But there is one race that I haven't seen,
and I haven't been able to stop thinking about it.
If they were here, we would know.
The giants!
For a nation of all races,
it's odd that I haven't seen a single giant.
I've only seen large humans.
Oh, really?
I guess you just haven't seen one yet.
Mama!
What do you want?
Ma... Mama... Ma, we... we... we have
brought those... those two here!
Okay.
Will you excuse me? It's a very busy day.
I hope you have a good afternoon, despite the bad weather!
What's wrong with you?
W-Well, I got nervous.
They're the real Germa 66.
Ichiji and Reiju were just as cool
as I thought they'd be.
Shut up! You're foolish to have been
influenced by a comic strip!
That they look "cool" couldn't matter less.
Let's see, what page was it?
Page 55.
Fifty-five.
There they are.
These two? I like the look on their faces.
Lick!
How long are you gonna keep us like this?!
Let me take a shower!
My body is covered in sticky syrup!
You look so sweet, Candy-chan. Lick!
Here comes Mama.
What?
Huh?
A transponder snail?!
It's been a while, Straw Hat Luffy!
You finally made it this far.
Is this Big Mom?
Let me out! I gotta go back!
I'm gonna get out of here,
even if I have to destroy everything!
Whoa-whoa, you've still
got that kind of spirit.
Since you didn't bring your entire crew,
I thought you'd forgotten what you said to me
on Fishman Island.
I'll kick your ass in the New World...
and make Fishman Island my territory!
Yeah, I'll kick your ass someday!
But right now we're just here
to take back Sanji!
I've had enough of your bluffs!
Shut up!
If you wanna fight, show yourself, Big Mom!
I'll fight you... right here!
Hey! Come on, Big Mom!
Show yourself!
I'll fight you!
Don't push your luck.
You're a rookie who just
entered the New World.
It's presumptuous of you
to request an audience with me.
They don't need my help in killing you.
Listen carefully, Straw Hat.
If you give up on Sanji completely,
I'll let you leave with your head.
Screw that!
Sanji and Pudding's wedding
is very...
special to me.
So sit there quietly
until everything is over.
Straw Hat, if you spoil what
I've been looking forward to,
I'll really make you pay for it!
Oh, yeah!
Do you remember?
When you ate all of the candy
that was made for me,
you gave me all the treasure
that you got from King Neptune.
We've got tons of treasure here.
I'll give all of it to you
as compensation for the candy!
Guess what we found in there!
Don't say that you want it back!
It's a legendary treasure box
that was passed down for
generations on Fishman Island:
the Tamate Box.
I wonder why Neptune let go of it.
It's certainly a national treasure.
I wonder what's in it.
I love treasure boxes!
So forget about the candy.
I'm going to open the Tamate Box
in front of everyone at the tea party tomorrow.
It's gonna be fun!
It's not gonna be fun! Sanji won't get married!
Damn!
Oh, yeah! I wanna see Pudding!
Luffy! Don't mention her!
I need to talk to her! She's my friend!
Huh? Friend?
Don't be absurd.
Why would the bride be your friend?
Luffy!
Stop joking around!
By the way, girl,
I heard you killed Lola.
What are you talking about?!
She's my friend!
She gave me the vivre card
as a token of friendship!
I'll put my signature on Mama's vivre card,
so if you run into trouble,
you can use this to find her.
When you see her, tell her I'm doing fine.
Thanks, Lola.
Lola was doing fine.
That's the message she sent.
There, I delivered it.
She told me that her mother was a pirate,
but I didn't expect that
it'd be Emperor Big Mom.
Lola thought that if I showed you
the vivre card, you'd help me...
You've gotta be joking!
I don't care if she's "doing fine."
I want her dead!
What?!
If you know where she is, tell me.
I'll send an assassin right away to kill her!
I'm surprised by the fact
she still thinks that we're family!
Children don't know how indebted they are
to their parents, and this proves it!
She's a dumb daughter who ran away,
rejecting the biggest-ever political marriage!
I'll never forgive her!
One of you can have me as a wife!
Especially you! Won't you marry me?!
Absalom is gonna marry me!
You're perfect for each other!
I thought I could give you all my support!
What?! Really?!
I'm here to save you, my friend!
Lola!
Lola! I'm so glad I got to see you again!
It's just for you,
because you and I are like sisters.
Lola...
If only...
she'd done what I said
and gotten married,
I could've gained tremendous power!
I'd already have beaten Kaido,
Red Hair, and even Whitebeard,
and I'd already be...
king of the pirates!
Lola's friend, Cat Burglar Nami.
I'll make you cough up where she is.
What a stupid story, Big Mom.
Lola's the one who didn't get married.
You're the one who
hasn't become king of the pirates.
That's all.
Luffy...
I'm here to pick another fight with you!
Don't be cocky just because
you're an emperor!
I'm going to take Sanji back!
And in the end, we're the ones who'll win!
What's going on-soir ?
Baron Tamago, it's the intruder!
The tiger mink is here!
No, he's a jaguar mink!
Pedro... He's already in the castle, as I thought.
Hey, wait, Big Mom!
You're so funny!
You've got to be kidding!
How could you pick a fight
with Mama in this castle?!
Shut up! Bring it on, you bastards!
Lola...
Hey, Big Brothers and Sisters!
Coming through! Coming through!
Anglaise, what's up?
We have an intrudee in the treasure room!
Coming through!
Do you mean an intruder, Anglaise?
Yeah, that's it!
And I'm not gonna brush my teeth today!
Coming through!
Please...
Everyone, get out of here safely.
Don't let him get away!
Get a move on!
Don't let him do whatever he wants!
The intruder's in the other area!
And now, in the Pirate Emperor
Big Mom's castle...
it's time to start...
a special live performance!
Aren't you angry, Mama?
Just because that squirt
picked a fight with me?
No way, Zeus! Think about it!
♪ Tomorrow, I'll gain Germa's power, ♪
♪ and even the Tamate Box... ♪
♪ I'll eat the most delicious ♪
♪ wedding cake ever, too! ♪
♪ Right? ♪
♪ That's right! ♪
♪ If I think of tomorrow, ♪
♪ I can tolerate anything! ♪
♪ How can I be angry?! ♪
♪ Tomorrow is going to be a great day! ♪
♪ A happy day! ♪
Oh? I received a signal. Mama!
They say that an intruder is causing trouble
near the treasure repository!
An intruder?
♪ Wedding cake! ♪
♪ Queen of the cakes! ♪
Don't tell me they're going after my Tamate Box!
Who is it?!
Oh, dammit, dammit!
Luffy and the others will be spared.
Big Mom promised me.
As long as I get married,
the Baratie will be okay, too.
Of course, it's hard to say goodbye to my friends,
but at least nobody will die!
That's all that really matters!
So, why am I so upset?
If I keep looking so tense,
my only source of hope,
Pudding-chan, will be sad!
I won't let your marriage with me be hell!
I'll be the lowest form of scum
if I make her worry.
Don't let a lovely girl like her be sad!
Be my usual self!
Yes! I'm a romantic cook!
Pudding-chan !
Pudding-chwan !
I'll make you happy!
Big Sis Lola's?
Yes. The girl had her vivre card,
and the homies in the Seducing Woods
were intimidated by it.
By the way, Madam Pudding,
the dress you chose yesterday was rejected by Mama.
Tomorrow, please wear the dress Mama chose.
Mama has planned out everything
after the wedding, too.
Also...
Madam Pudding, it's still raining in the yard.
Madam Pudding?
Pudding, as long as you do
what I say, you'll be all right.
You look just like a doll, Pudding.
Good girl, Pudding.
She's not gonna kill me.
After all, we're family.
I wanna choose my own husband!
I can't believe they let this happen
the day before the tea party!
There he is!
So quick!
This is it, intruder!
Shoot!
Shoot him down!
Run!
Where is he now?!
He went downstairs
to the third floor of the midbaum,
near the courtyard!
It won't be easy to take him down!
Corner him in the garden-soir !
Roger!
I can't handle any more soldiers!
There you are, intruder.
Well, there are a lot less than before.
Only Pedro-san could've done that!
What kind of creature are you?
You're very strange, even for this country.
I agree.
Mama would be happy.
Get him!
Hey, Baron Tamago!
Commander Smoothie!
You were right. There's another one.
That one is bait, like you said.
Damn you, Pedro!
You created a big mess!
We let him get into the treasure repository,
and then he locked the door.
Sorry. It's my fault.
But there is only one entrance
to the treasure repository.
Even if he can steal the treasure, it's impossible for him to run from you, Commander Smoothie.
As long as you guard the door closely,
there won't be a problem-dezvous.
You're right. You can count on me.
If he defeats the guards inside and comes out,
I'll kill him. Is that okay?
No, the man inside is probably a skeleton-bon.
Mama would love to have that strange beast.
Defeat him, but don't kill him!
Got it.
Pedro-san told me...
that through Big Mom's ability,
you are all infused with human souls.
That means you Chess Peacekeepers are...
driven by soul!
Oh, no!
How powerful!
Wait a second!
It's not tuned yet!
Tear him apart!
This is it, you damn skeleton!
Oh, please!
W-W-W-W-Wait, wait!
Please wait!
What happened?!
You don't know my other name,
do you, baby?
They call me Soul King!
The Chess Peacekeepers!
The soldiers infused with souls...
cannot stay on their feet...
in the presence of my Soul Scream!
Enough with that!
Oh, this is unexpected.
What do you need, Pudding?
Pudding?
Hey! Pudding! Get us outta here! We got caught!
No, Luffy!
The other guys are listening too!
What brought you to a place like this?
Brother Opera, do you mind if I talk to Luffy-kun
and his companion for a moment?
Luffy-kun ? Sure, go ahead.
Let me put a bookmark here.
Pudding...
You two...
Hey, Pudding!
We went to the coast!
Stop it! Pudding will be in trouble!
You got beaten up.
Luffy-kun.
Nami-chan.
I'm sure my brothers and sisters
did horrible things to you.
I'm sorry!
– No...
– Don't...
I couldn't go to the coast
where we promised to meet, either...
I'm really sorry!
That's okay. Raise your head, please.
Why are they whispering?
I actually...
was proposed to by Sanji-san.
– What?!
It made me happy.
But...
I know Sanji-san is just being nice to me.
I'm causing everyone trouble.
That's not true...
So, don't worry.
I'm not going to marry him.
Listen.
Hey, wait, Pudding!
Goodbye.
Mirro-world, Brûlée's House
Whole Cake
Island
Capital
Sweet City
Whole Cake Chateau Library
Prisoner Library
Whole Cake Chateau
Perospero
Eldest Son of the Charlotte Family
Sanji's Guest Room
Queen's Chamber
Pudding's Room
Bishop
m 255 549 l 258 629 520 634 521 549
Pawn
m 746 130 l 743 209 944 205 941 131
Knight
m 194 126 l 374 128 376 200 196 196
Rook
m 746 547 l 944 550 943 627 750 628
King
m 386 550 l 599 551 600 628 396 628
Queen
m 545 175 l 539 253 780 248 785 172
Prisoner Library