One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Ka...
Kawa...
Kawamatsu?!
Is it...
really you?!
You're alive!
I am... despite having eaten nothing but
rotten fish for the past thirteen years.
Let me see your face, Kawamatsu!
Alas, I am in shackles.
What?!
When will the battle start?
Nine days from now,
on the night of the Fire Festival!
Chopping off Kaido's head during his own
festival is a great way to pay tribute to him!
Forgive me, Raizo, but could you
help me get out of here first?!
Of course I will! I'll get right to it!
It seems I will need the keys to both the cage
and the cuffs before I can free you.
Indeed. Although the rust
may inhibit their opening.
There's someone at the forbidden cell!
Who's that?!
That's the guy!
Master Solitaire!
We found the key thief
from the Executive Tower!
Don't let him escape!
Oh no!
Smoke Escape Technique!
He vanished!
He must be a ninja!
Find him!
All right, leave the key thief
to the others and...
bring the thing here!
Alright...
We've got some fools to execute!
– Yes, sir!
Hey! Come this way!
Here we go!
Give it up for Superstar Queen's
Special Device Performance:
The Sumo Inferno!
Sumo?
What the...?!
This is the same collar
we just put on you guys!
Imagine this stone pillar is you!
Leave the ring with that thing on and...
How scary!
As you just saw, the moment you go
out of bounds, sharp blades are ejected,
instantly lopping off your head!
Damn! It's just like
the Celestial Dragons' collars!
And of course it's designed so that you can't
forcibly remove it, so don't even try!
You'll be fine as long as you
keep winning sumo matches!
But leaving the ring is instant death!
You're a tag team! Consider the execution
a success once you're both outside the ring!
But if you change your mind
and join our crew,
I'll spare you alone, Straw Hat!
Our side will use weapons,
fight in numbers, and won't be wearing collars!
We'll deploy as many people as we want.
That's why I'll do you this one favor:
I'll remove your seastone cuffs!
Wh-Whaaat?!
After all the trouble I went to!
Wait, does that mean this is not
the key to Sir Luffy's cuffs?!
Yay!
You're a nice guy after all!
This means you're letting us out!
Aren't you forgetting about the collar?
Now there's something worse on you!
Oh, yeah.
Wait a minute!
I will just hold Straw Hat back
if we're on the same team!
Could you at least execute us separately?!
Hey, balloon!
Balloon?!
Straw Hat!
If I kick your ass...
will you let us out of here?!
There you are.
You're the one who stole my sword, right?
It is not your sword...
The named blade Shusui has already
been returned to where it belongs.
It's a treasure that was stolen from the grave
of the legendary samurai of Wano, Ryuma!
I'm aware!
Then keep quiet and turn back!
Or I will also claim those two swords
strapped to your waist!
A weapon collector, huh?
What are you gonna do with all those?
As it happens, we could do
with a bunch of weapons, too,
so your timing's perfect.
That collection of yours...
I'm gonna take the whole thing!
Not if I bring you down first, mountain bandit!
I'm sorry if you misunderstood...
but I'm...
a pirate!
You crack me up.
Your Awesomeness!
He'll understand once it starts!
He just doesn't get how rigged this game is!
He's clueless about his odds for survival!
You're right!
Get ready to enter the ring, guys!
– Deathmatch! Deathmatch! Deathmatch!
Th-There are too many of them...!
Not to mention, we're armed to the teeth.
No weapons for you!
Is it sinking in that you're dead men walking?!
– Deathmatch! Deathmatch!
– Deathmatch! Deathmatch! Deathmatch!
Rest in peace, old man Hyo and Straw Hat...
Lock eyes with your opponents!
Ready...!
Begin!
The rest of your prisoners, watch and learn!
This is what happens when you defy a guard!
Who's next?! They're not
even a good warm-up!
– Whaaat?!
Did he just use...?!
So he's got conqueror's haki.
You...
Looks like this is gonna be interesting.
Pleasures, enter the ring!
Things have gotten quite rowdy
since he showed up...
Just don't let Boss Hyogoro die.
I'm counting on you, Luffytaro.
It's a raid!
That's Hawkins, a Headliner
for the Beast Pirates!
Nobody move!
What could you possibly
want with a bathhouse?
Inspecting a bathhouse is ideal...
because everyone's naked
and we can see everything.
Drake, what are you doing? Get inside.
I'm only tasked to take down
that Soba Mask idiot.
You can do your own dirty work.
What do we do, Shinobu?!
They probably know about us.
They came for us.
It's not fair! We're vulnerable here!
Should we fight?
As a last resort.
Mature women shouldn't
draw their weapons recklessly.
Hide behind me.
Everyone, line up and show us your ankles!
– What?!
Anyone with a reversed crescent moon
tattoo on their ankle is coming with us!
That means getting out of the tub, too!
I can't believe it. How does he know?!
Search them.
– Yes, sir!
Was the plan leaked?
Someone's back there!
Show yourself!
Nami! I've got your back if anything happens.
Sorry, I wasn't trying to hide!
I'm just another patron.
You...!
– Dynamite!
– Oh, my! She's a national treasure!
How devastating!
I can't believe it!
That's beyond powerful, Nami!
It's her Happiness Punch!
What...?
Is that...? He's the guy from yesterday.
Soba Mask!
Na... mi...
The shape of Nami's body was magnificent
like a mighty flowing river...
Sanji! What's he doing here?!
What's he wearing?! Is this a joke?!
Drake!
Soba Mask?!
He was inside all along!
Hey! Where's Soba Mask?!
What?!
Where–
You should've told me that
you're shy around naked women!
I'm not...
Drake... you're from the North Blue, right?
So are you... What of it?
Then you're familiar with him, correct?
That's Germa 66's...
Stealth Black!
Stop running!
We're still searchin–
Here's our chance!
Go to hell, Germa 66!
Soba Mask!
Is it Stealth Black's transmission device?!
Hang on tight!
He's flying! After him!
That's Stealth Black for you...!
I'll get him next time!
Sanji, care to explain?!
It's a long story! I'll tell you later!
Aren't you losing a lot of blood?
I could die happy right now!
Anyway, it's a pain that they've
caught on to the ankle tattoos!
Yes... I wonder how they found out...
On my way to the bathhouse,
I overheard some more bad news.
Bepo's group was captured!
– What?
It seems the Beast Pirates
are using Traf's crew as bait.
I'm sure he'll want to rescue them.
They're his crew, after all.
We can't let him.
The Flower Capital would fall into chaos!
And you were wasting time
doing what exactly?
I wanna have some oshiruko already.
Hey, haven't we reached that Udon place yet?
Chopperemon!
I'm starving.
Don't drool when you look at me!
It won't be long now, Olin!
When we get to Udon,
we'll save Big Bro Luffy.
And then...
we'll have...
some oshiruko soup!
You like it too, Otama?
Yup, I love it!
Miss Otsuru treated me
to some for my birthday!
My mouth slowly filled with
the sweetness of the red-bean paste...
It truly tickled my taste buds.
I know!
Red-bean paste is the best!
Yes! Yes! Absolutely!
Uh-huh! Uh-huh!
Red-bean paste! And mochi!
It was the softest and tastiest
thing I've ever had!
I know, I know!
Mochi shines just like a frog's eyeball!
What?!
A frog's eyeball?
Olin, that's a little freaky.
Oh, really?
Well, when I think about it...
I can't help drooling.
I'm not edible!
I really can't wait to have some oshiruko!
They are getting quite excited
about the oshiruko.
It's no good.
What should I do?
When she learns there is no oshiruko,
the shock might restore her memories,
and she'll be Big Mom again!
Straw Hat!
Instead of saving Luffy,
we'd be putting him in harm's way!
What should I do?!
What am I supposed to do?!
Get some more soup!
Yes, sir!
Luffytaro wins!
You did it, Luffytaro!
Incredible! You beat all the Pleasures...!
That's not it.
What's not it? You won again!
Well, Rayleigh did it so easily.
Rayleigh?
Yeah.
Luffy...
imagine that using armament haki
is like wearing invisible armor.
Back then, Rayleigh sent that elephant flying without touching it.
The first time he showed me haki,
it was really advanced.
If only I could do that...!
We're getting nowhere with this!
If you lemme at 'em, we'd wrap up
the execution in no time!
You don't get the appeal of the Sumo Inferno!
Look,
fights are most engaging when
they're given time and numbers.
It'll slowly sap his spirit and energy until
he succumbs to a miserable death.
"We'd wrap up the execution in no time"?!
Don't be so dense.
That's not exciting at all!
Seconds please!
Again?! You've already had
so much red-bean soup!
Screw you! Red-bean soup
is like oxygen to me!
Here you go.
No one else can have any!
It's my oshiruko because it's my favorite!
It's my soup!
Send my opponent flying
as if I'm wearing invisible armor!
Sir Straw Hat, what are you...?
Alright!
I wanna practice! Bring it on!
I met Ryuma.
Don't lie to me!
You met Ryuma?!
Do you expect me to believe such drivel?!
Well, his soul belonged to
someone else I know.
Quit talking gibberish!
How could you know Ryuma?!
Ryuma was a great swordsman
capable of besting any opponent in an instant!
You have no clue how valuable
the named blade Shusui is!
Shusui is Wano's sacred treasure!
It belongs to Ryuma!
Long ago, when the outside world
considered Wano to be a land of gold...
Gold? What are you talking about?
Wide open!
Pirates all over the world craved our gold.
Nobles sought to rule Wano, this land of gold!
But one man showed those foreign invaders
just how formidable he was...
and etched Wano's samurai
deep in their minds!
That is the kind of man Ryuma was.
There are countless legends about
his feats as a swordsman.
For instance...
it is said that he once slew a dragon
that was flying over the capital!
After his death, honored as
Wano's God of the Blade,
he was laid to rest in a temple
with the named blade Shusui.
Shusui is a national treasure!
Okay. I get it.
But you missed the part
where I'm supposed to care!
I'm gonna take back Shusui!
Two swords just doesn't feel right to me.
Is that not an overestimation
of your worthiness?
Shusui is a black blade!
In other words, it was forged
through the battles that Ryuma fought!
I was merely ascertaining whether you were
a spineless whelp with no true stake to the blade!
"Forged"?
Oh, yeah, I was wondering about that...
Help!
Wide open!
You bastard...!
Stop trying to catch me
when my guard is down!
Finding an opening is essential in a fight
to the death! That's all I've been doing!
Somebody, help! Someone is trying to kill us!
Ah! There's a samurai!
Hey! Help us!
Are they serious or just
fooling around? I can't tell!
Swordsmen, please help!
Hmm? Blood?
I guess they're not joking.
Hold it right there!
Wide open!
Can't you wait?!
Hey, take a hint!
Our duel is not over!
I'll finish the damn duel! Just wait a minute!
You're the murderer... Zorojuro, right?
Zorojuro, why would you
wanna help that woman?
Why do you wanna slash her?
I'm only after the brat
that won't stop laughing.
Don't worry, Toko.
Kamzo the Reaper.
You're known as an indiscriminate street
slasher in the capital, but in actuality...
you're Orochi's assassin
disguised as an outlaw!
Why else would you be after Otoko?
I see you don't address
the shogun by his title.
Who are you anyway?
Lord Samurai, please help us!
Well, of course, I'm not gonna just stand here
and watch a kid and a woman get killed...
I will repay you any way I can!
I wouldn't mind some food and sake.
Done.
Alright! Deal!
Fine by me. I've been authorized
to kill anyone that gets in my way.
Taking out lackeys like you
usually upsets the boss.
Don't worry!
You're the one that's gonna die!
He's pretty tough!
Looks like you're getting serious.
Still feels like something's missing.
I'm beary hungry!
If I beat Straw Hat, can you bear
to give me all the prisoners' dumplings?
Sure. Go wild!
That's beary Queen of you!
This bear's a hundred times
more motivated now!
What?!
Let's bear it and go!
Bear!
Those punches...
bearly hurt!
Sir Straw Hat!
He might look adorable, but he's still a bear!
They say that a bear's claws are
sharp enough to rip humans limb from limb!
Be careful!
Bear!
Send him flying...
without making contact!
Damn, when I put power behind it,
I end up hitting them anyway!
What are you...
attempting to do?
Forget it.
Let's keep going!
Next!
Wide open!
I can't pull it out!
I'll make do with this for now...
Three...
swords?!
Three-Sword Style!
Purgatory...
Oni Giri!
How fearsome...
Damn... This isn't even the final battle!
L-Lord Samurai!
m 1311 0 l 1275 67.5 1272 126 1306.5 151.5 1473 150 1503 121.5 1500 36 1467 0 m 0 607.5 l 160.5 607.5 160.5 736.5 0 736.5 m 1129.5 621 l 1282.5 621 1311 660 1311 727.5 1278 757.5 1132.5 757.5 1110 735 1108.5 654
Ringo
Udon
Hakumai
m 31.5 1.5 l 166.5 0 193.5 25.5 193.5 115.5 24 120 0 99 m 301.5 4.5 l 445.5 4.5 468 30 469.5 118.5 306 120 292.5 106.5 m 786 0 l 1080 0 1080 127.5 786 127.5
Kuri
Kibi
Flower
Capital
m -103.5 -72 l 112.5 -72 112.5 102 -103.5 102
Wano
Ringo
Wano's Prisoner
Mining Camp in Udon
A Bathhouse
Flower Capital
Bearman
Bear SMILE Fruit
A Gifter
Bearman
Bear SMILE Fruit
A Gifter