One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
The Great Pirate Era...
has proven to be a more tumultuous storm
than the World Government expected.
The figures in the eye of this
relentless tempest are…
Monkey D. Luffy...
and the Straw Hat Pirates!
To confront the furious Great Pirate Era,
fifty world leaders have come together
for this quadrennial conference:
the Reverie, which will commence shortly.
Now is a time of great change.
At Sea in the New World
I'm hungry!
What's this?
Where did you get that?!
Huh? I just found it in my pocket.
Cool! Is it real?
What is it?
Don't you remember?
It's what Germa used to transform!
Oh, that's right!
I'm gonna transform with it!
Wait! I'll go first!
– Sanji!
I'm getting rid of it.
– What?!
Don't you dare throw it out!
Do it, and I'll look for it on the ocean floor!
I'd love to see an anchor like you try!
It was in my pocket. If you don't
want it, let me have it instead!
No, let me have it! Please!
No way!
But I wonder how it
ended up in Luffy's pocket.
It must've been Niji.
He did it as a dig against me.
I don't want my strength to come
from their crappy technology!
Think about it, Sanji!
Science is a noble
human power!
Why do you care so much?!
– If we used the raid suit...
– maybe we could shoot beams!
Are you guys children?!
Franky already does that just fine!
We've got enough freaks on our crew.
No! It's mine!
What? Were you making light of science?
Nami my sweet!
There's no way I'd insult your science!
My Sorcery Climate Baton is the fusion of
sky science and Usopp's engineering!
Look!
I just love being inside her baton!
Zeus?!
You actually tagged along?!
I can't believe food outweighs
your loyalty to Big Mom!
♪ I got myself a powerful servant! ♪
N-Nami...
Zeus, remember this...
I've been serving Nami since
long before you came along!
But I get to live in the baton
she keeps on her at all times!
Huh?!
Sanji, you're arguing with water vapor.
Alright! Let's go!
– Why isn't it working?!
Stop whining!
I guess it only works on you!
Show us already!
Shut up!
I'm not part of Germa!
Listen up! "Germa 66" and "Vinsmoke" are
two names I never want to hear again!
Thank you!
Please transform!
L-Let go of me, you morons!
Hey, everybody!
The newspaper's here!
Is there anything about us?
Let's see...
A close-up of Luffy!
What about Jinbe?
Does it say what happened after we left?
Uh... Jinbe, Jinbe…
No word of what happened after we left...
Only that "Luffy, Sanji, Jinbe, and Bege made
an assassination attempt on Big Mom's life."
And that "Luffy was the mastermind"!
"Mastermind"?!
Oh, bounty posters!
My bounty went up!
It's 330 million berries!
For real?!
Wait, what was Moss Head's at?
I think Zoro's was at...
320 million berries!
I did it!
I'm higher than that damn Moss Head!
It's just a number.
They changed "only alive"
back to "dead or alive"!
Huh? What's wrong?
My name...
It says "Vinsmoke Sanji"!
Makes sense...
GLOOM...
My bounty only increased
because of Germa's infamy!
S-Sanji! Are you okay?!
Huh?! There's an even gloomier
aura coming from over there!
GLOOM...
DOOM...
L-Luffy!
GLOOM...
What's wrong?!
The Fifth Emperor
Meanwhile...
The world is abuzz with talk of the Reverie...
the global summit held every four years
in the Holy Land of Mary Geoise.
This is Fishman Island,
10,000 meters below sea level.
The Ryugu Kingdom.
He did it-jamon!
Jinbe finally joined Luffy's crew!
It's unbelievable to think the two of them
fought together against Big Mom.
King Neptune
Ryugu Kingdom
I wonder if they escaped on the same ship.
Manboshi
Ryuboshi
Jinbe and Straw Hat-fa-so-la-ti-do! ♪
Manboshi
Ryuboshi
Fukuboshi
Manboshi
Ryuboshi
Fukuboshi
Manboshi
Ryuboshi
Fukuboshi
Of course they did. The article
says Big Mom was furious.
Manboshi
Ryuboshi
Fukuboshi
Manboshi
Ryuboshi
Fukuboshi
Manboshi
Ryuboshi
Fukuboshi
Manboshi
Ryuboshi
Fukuboshi
Manboshi
Ryuboshi
Fukuboshi
Manboshi
Ryuboshi
Fukuboshi
Manboshi
Ryuboshi
Fukuboshi
Manboshi
Ryuboshi
Fukuboshi
Manboshi
Ryuboshi
Fukuboshi
Manboshi
Ryuboshi
Fukuboshi
Manboshi
Ryuboshi
Fukuboshi
Manboshi
Ryuboshi
Fukuboshi
Manboshi
Ryuboshi
Fukuboshi
Manboshi
Ryuboshi
Fukuboshi
Manboshi
Ryuboshi
Fukuboshi
Manboshi
Ryuboshi
Fukuboshi
Manboshi
Ryuboshi
Fukuboshi
Manboshi
Ryuboshi
Fukuboshi
Manboshi
Ryuboshi
Fukuboshi
Manboshi
Ryuboshi
Fukuboshi
Manboshi
Ryuboshi
Fukuboshi
Manboshi
Ryuboshi
Fukuboshi
Manboshi
Ryuboshi
Fukuboshi
Manboshi
Ryuboshi
Fukuboshi
Manboshi
Ryuboshi
Fukuboshi
Manboshi
Ryuboshi
Fukuboshi
Manboshi
Ryuboshi
Fukuboshi
Manboshi
Ryuboshi
Fukuboshi
Manboshi
Ryuboshi
Fukuboshi
Manboshi
Ryuboshi
Fukuboshi
Manboshi
Ryuboshi
Fukuboshi
Manboshi
Ryuboshi
Fukuboshi
Manboshi
Ryuboshi
Fukuboshi
Manboshi
Ryuboshi
Fukuboshi
Manboshi
Ryuboshi
Fukuboshi
Manboshi
Ryuboshi
Fukuboshi
Manboshi
Ryuboshi
Fukuboshi
Manboshi
Ryuboshi
Fukuboshi
Manboshi
Ryuboshi
Fukuboshi
Manboshi
Ryuboshi
Fukuboshi
Manboshi
Ryuboshi
Fukuboshi
Manboshi
Ryuboshi
Fukuboshi
Manboshi
Ryuboshi
Fukuboshi
Manboshi
Ryuboshi
Fukuboshi
Manboshi
Ryuboshi
Fukuboshi
Manboshi
Ryuboshi
Fukuboshi
Manboshi
Ryuboshi
Fukuboshi
Manboshi
Ryuboshi
Fukuboshi
Manboshi
Ryuboshi
Fukuboshi
Manboshi
Ryuboshi
Fukuboshi
Manboshi
Ryuboshi
Fukuboshi
Manboshi
Ryuboshi
Fukuboshi
Manboshi
Ryuboshi
Fukuboshi
Manboshi
Ryuboshi
Fukuboshi
We must officially declare that our country
is under the Straw Hats' protection-jamon!
Dearest Father! Dearest Brothers!
Shirahoshi.
Princess Shirahoshi
Allow me to attend the Reverie with you!
I have to go, or Sir Luffy
will call me Wimpyhoshi again!
I've been waiting for you to come around!
Alright, let's go!
Let's!
However, overshadowing the upcoming Reverie
and stunning the public is the news that
rookie pirate Straw Hat Luffy
threatened Emperor Big Mom,
someone whose position hadn't
wavered in decades.
The article states the following:
"A reliable source has confirmed
that Straw Hat Luffy
has taken command of
seven powerful pirate crews.
This move makes him
the commander of 5,000 subordinates.
Of note, both Ace and the Revolutionary
Army's number two, Sabo,
are considered his sworn brothers.
He convinced the evil army Germa 66,
the Sun Pirates, and the Fire Tank Pirates
to follow him without hesitation,
all due to his leadership and charisma.
His guileful strategy resulted in
the destruction of the queen's castle.
He felled two of her commanders worth
800 million and 1 billion respectively.
Therefore, it is natural to consider
Straw Hat Luffy the victor!"
And so, the article concludes
with a proclamation:
"The Fifth Emperor has emerged!"
What's all this "Fifth Emperor" garbage?!
It's just pirate scum causing trouble,
whether it's Four Emperors or Five Emperors.
Fleet Admiral Sakazuki
Marine Headquarters
I have a report for you,
Fleet Admiral Sakazuki!
En route to the Reverie,
pirates ambushed the ship from Lulusia!
The king was unharmed,
but Princess Comane has been kidnapped.
Where was the Marine escort?!
Check.
Grandfather! Grandfather!
What is it, Rebecca?
Look!
“Assassins Make Attempt on Big Mom's Life"
So? Have you read the news about Lucy?!
Rebecca
A Dressrosan Lady-in-Waiting
Yes. Indeed I have.
Oh, okay...
Luffyland is amazing!
That's our boss for you!
The article mentioned us too.
Commander Leo
Tonta Corps, Tontatta Tribe
Everyone, once we reach the Holy Land,
you must not talk about this.
What? Why not?
We may be indebted to him,
but the World Government
and the Marines see him differently.
You're right! He's a pirate!
Exactly. And he's now gaining
an extraordinarily dangerous reputation.
He's really something.
Oh, yeah! I've got to show Viola!
Let's show her!
No mistaking it. Those ships belong
to the Kingdoms of Dressrosa and Prodence!
There's no Marine escort either!
Oh! Th-That's Princess Viola!
She's as gorgeous as they say.
Is that other girl also a royal?
We'll get to name our price
if we kidnap 'em too.
Right, Princess Comane?
Just call Papa already!
He'll pay you as much as you want!
This is why I like royal families!
Just hold out a bit longer.
We're pretty damn greedy.
Anyway, they won't see us coming...
since we're hidden underwater!
Sink 'em!
Roger!
It's impossible to guard against a torpedo!
What...?!
An ambush?!
Ready the cannons!
– Yes, sir!
Don't! There's no need!
I'm glad I made it in time!
You're safe now!
A-Are you a Marine?
Captain Koby
Marine Headquarters
I'm Captain Koby of Marine Headquarters!
Did we miss the target?!
That's impossible!
We're gonna sink!
You're not hurt, are you?
Your party came from
Dressrosa and Prodence, right?
You must be tired, traveling so far.
What just happened?
How did you get here?
I had to go on ahead of my ship.
Just now, pirates were
targeting you from underwater.
"Underwater"...?
You mean by a torpedo?!
I'm glad they missed!
Me too.
Helmeppo! Report!
We caught the pirates!
Look!
Lieutenant Commander Helmeppo
Marine Headquarters
Princess Comane from Lulusia is okay too!
Why you little...!
Roast these jerks on a skewer!
They need to pay!
Of course, they'll pay dearly, Princess!
Anyway, what's the deal with your
observation haki, Koby?!
I never even sensed the torpedo.
A submarine...?
You have to be careful with
pirates these days...
That was close.
Hello!
So, you're the famous Captain Koby!
What?
From the Rocky Port Incident?
Trafalgar Law, one of the Worst Generation,
was the mastermind behind that incident.
You're the hero who protected the citizens.
N-No, I'm no hero!
You're not just brave,
you're a fine young man!
Wow... This guy is strong...
He just saved us from a torpedo,
yet he doesn't want any credit?
Thank you!
It's nothing...
Oh! Luffy!
I mean, it's Straw Hat Luffy!
The front-page article caught my eye.
Do you wanna read it, Koby?
No, no. Well, I mean, you know...
"The Fifth Emperor."
Luffy's still as cool as ever!
He keeps moving forward!
Koby?
Every time I see you in the paper,
I think back to that day...
Hey, Captain Koby!
What are you doing? Come back already!
Right!
Thank you so much!
Sure.
Seeing how close we are to New Marineford,
allow us to escort you the rest of the way!
I give you my thanks.
Oh, hey!
What is it?
Do you like Lucy, Koby?
You like Luffyland, right?
N-No! H-He's my enemy!
Can't fool us!
We won't tell.
Stay and chat.
K-Kindly let go! I-I'm with the Marines!
But you looked so happy
when you read the paper.
Th-That's because...
Come on. Let's talk!
P-Please stop!
Oh, Luffyland is in this article here too!
He is?!
So you do like him!
Damn...
Having my bounty increase
because of Germa's reputation...
is so depressing.
Hey, are you all right?
Do your wounds hurt?
N-No!
My...
My bounty went down!
Look!
It's 150 million berries!
– What?!
Really?! I thought it just increased
to 500 million recently!
One hundred fifty million is lower
than your bounty two years ago!
How is that even possible?!
Did you do something wrong?!
Wouldn't that make it bigger?
Oh, that's right.
It's not so bad.
Fewer people will come after us.
Nami!
Luffy is our captain!
This could harm our reputation!
This sucks! Why?!
A Port Town
Kingdom of Lulusia, Grand Line
Prepare the cannons!
Fire at will!
Let's go!
Grab their money and valuables!
Where are the Marines?!
Didn't they already arrive to help?!
They destroyed our ship!
Damn!
To hell with the Marines!
Their king's gone to the Reverie.
All their best soldiers went away with him!
A defenseless country is just
begging pirates to raid it!
Now listen good!
I'm affiliated with Blackbeard,
one of the Four Emperors!
I have been dubbed Pinkbeard!
Captain Pinkbeard
Pinkbeard Pirates
Bounty:   52 Million
Remember my name!
Fear Blackbeard!
All right, men!
In the name of Blackbeard, take everything!
Okay, hand over your money!
P-Please stop!
It's no use hiding!
We'll burn the whole town down!
Come on!
Let's get out of here!
Hey, catch that girl!
Stop right there!
What's that in your arms?
Gimme a gander at what
you're holding so tightly!
This is...
Huh? Just milk?!
And here I thought it was money...
Screw it! I'll take it anyway.
You can't! This is for the village children!
Put a sock in it!
You're being awful obstinate about this!
Please give it back!
That milk...
We can't go without it!
Huh?!
Then bring us your money instead!
What?
I don't have any.
Don't you have a heavenly tribute fund?
Th-The heavenly tribute is for
the king and the Celestial Dragons.
It's all we can do to scrimp
and save every day!
We'll face execution if we don't
pay the heavenly tribute!
What?!
Your king sounds terrible!
Well, alright!
Hey, men, get searching!
They're hiding the heavenly tribute!
The money's stashed away!
Take all they've got!
But why?!
C'mon! Tell us where the tribute is!
Leave us alone...
This town is poor.
P-Please, anything but the fund!
Let go!
Somebody...
You wouldn't have gotten hurt
if you'd just given up!
Kill anyone who resists!
I'm begging you!
Please just leave us alone!
Shut up!
Go, Morley!
Who the hell are you?
Why's it shaking?
Is there something underground?!
The hell?!
A giant trident?!
Is that a giant?
One, two! One, two!
One, two! One...
two!
A giant just climbed
straight from the ground!
And he's dressed really weird!
Um, why is he wearing a miniskirt?
Gross! Just where do you
think you're looking?!
Why are you staring at me?!
Do you have a crush on me or something?!
You're actually accusing me of that?!
What's this dirty old man's deal?!
Just shoot him! Shoot him dead!
Say what?!
Stop fawning over me, sillies!
D-Do giants live underground?!
First one I've ever seen...
Who is he anyway?
Don't be so mean!
Come on!
How's this possible?! He's pushing
the ground around like clay!
Don't waver! It's just his power!
Incredible!
So...? What'll you do now?
You servile...
pieces of trash.
What? Trash?
What should we do?
Excuse me!
Who are...? Who are you people?
Oh, my!
Come now, come now!
Wait just a tick, Morley!
What do you want?
Oh, please! I wanted to take
my latest invention out for a spin,
but you ran on ahead!
Who are these people?!
A murder of crows?!
Captain!
Huh?!
S-Someone's on the roof!
What?!
The crows are gathering...!
How dare you hurt those
who offer no resistance.
Captain Pinkbeard... those four...!
They're usually scattered around the world!
They're the commanders...
of the Revolutionary Army!
Wh... Wh...
What?!
Commander Morley
Western Division
Revolutionary Army
Hey, they're still staring at me.
Commander Belo Betty
Eastern Division
Revolutionary Army
Keep your shirts on, trash!
Commander Lindbergh
Southern Division
Revolutionary Army
Allow me to test my new weapon!
Commander Karasu
Northern Division
Revolutionary Army
You're done getting your way.
The commanders of...
the Revolutionary Army?
Heehaw!
Officer Emporio Ivankov
Revolutionary Army
That Straw-boy sure is something!
He certainly has your blood.
Commander in Chief Monkey D. Dragon
Revolutionary Army
And...
who knew that Sanji-boy
vass a Germa 66 prince?!
He never spoke a voord of it to me!
Vhaat a rascal!
This debacle led to Germa's expulsion
from the World Government.
I expected nothing less
of Straw-boy and Sanji-boy.
They are the driving force
of the Great Pirate Era!
Officer Inazuma
Revolutionary Army
Hack
Soldier
Revolutionary Army
The Straw Hats... Vhaat excitement!
Anyway, the commanders are late.
Koala
Assistant Fishman Karate Instructor
Revolutionary Army
They should have arrived by now.
That is true...
By the vayy, Sabo...
vhaat are you doing over there?
He's been grinning since reading the news
about Luffy, so his face cramped up, didn't it?
Vhaat a dum-dum!
Lindbergh here!
What's wrong? Everyone's waiting.
Is this Sabo?
We're almost there.
But we ran into some trouble!
Mind if we're a bit late?
Got it. Just stay in one piece.
Oh, I'm so excited!
All of the Revolutionary Army's
officers will be here!
I get to see Commander Morley!
Mistress Betty is my favorite!
Sabo, the clock is ticking. We need to start.
It'd be best if we finalize
the plan before they arrive.
You're up, Chief of Staff.
Yeah.
At the upcoming Reverie, we'll finally...
...declare war...
Chief of Staff Sabo
Revolutionary Army
against the Celestial Dragons.
So they're...
the commanders of...
the Revolutionary Army!
Why are four of their officers here?!
Gosh, you boys play rough!
Maybe because they're keen
on you, you giant lug!
No way. That's icky!
I checked in with Sabo,
so shall we begin, Betty?!
There's no stopping me.
Looks like they won't answer my question.
And what's that guy mumbling
about over there?!
I deem your actions unforgivable!
Why's he so pissed?!
What's it gonna be, you pieces of trash?!
Will you die?
Or will you fight?!
Choose your destiny!
Why leave being a hero to someone else?!
You could be heroes!
The townspeople picked up sticks!
C'mon! Don't make me laugh!
Are you gonna fight us?!
I don't know why, but I'm inspired
and feel a surge of energy!
Let's drive these pirates out of here!
We should fight to protect our country!
That's right!
This is the power of Betty's Rally-Rally Fruit!
By waving her flag, she can awaken
the latent power in anyone!
Betty is the flag-bearer of freedom!
Now, charge!
I don't think they know it hurts to get shot!
Gotta put you in your place!
Lind! Karasu! Back them up!
Got it!
Take this!
Cool Shooter!
That's cold!
My gun just froze over!
You rotten bastards!
Get out of here, you pirates!
Don't waver! Cut them down!
Take their weapons!
The crows took our swords!
Give 'em back!
Don't stop!
Don't give in to fate!
Fight!
Get lost!
What's gotten into them all of a sudden?!
Give me...
back...
my milk!
Let's scram!
This isn't over!
Pinkbeard... has a bounty of 52 million.
Emperor Blackbeard will come after you...
Unfortunately for you,
that man cares little for his men.
Hey, boy! Shut your pie hole already!
Hey, you yellow-bellied,
weak-kneed, pathetic clowns!
If you turn him in to the World Government...
you can claim his bounty.
That's 52 million berries.
And...
it's all yours!
Also, I want you to have this.
Use this to contact the Revolutionary Army.
You did great...
What?
Call us any time.
We'll never turn our backs...
on the weaklings who want to rise up.
M-Mistress Belo Betty!
Thank you for everything, Revolutionary Army!
Hey, what are we meeting up for this time?
We're gonna pick a fight
with the Celestial Dragons.
Oh, that's the best news ever! I can't wait!
Oh, and Karasu!
Turn on your voice amplifier.
I forgot.
Two days remain before the Reverie begins.
All the pieces from around the world
are beginning to coalesce.
Okay, roger that.
That was the others, Sabo.
They'll arrive shortly.
All right!
Let's get a move on.
What the hell?!
Why was that punk who screwed
with my valuable SMILE trade deal...
Kaido, "King of the Beasts"
One of the Four Emperors
in that old hag's territory?!
Oh, so he's the victor?!
Huh?!
When exactly did I lose?!
It was him, Mama! He printed this article!
Oh, you'll pay for this, Morgans–
No!
The one who'll really pay...
Charlotte "Big Mom" Linlin
One of the Four Emperors
is Straw Hat!
An Emperor?
Marshall D. "Blackbeard" Teach
One of the Four Emperors
It's a bit premature to call you that!
"Red-Haired" Shanks
One of the Four Emperors
Looks like I'll be seeing you soon...
Luffy!
So, your bounty fell. What can we do?
Cheer up, Luffy.
Let me help in some way.
Let's do what we can!
Do you want me to cook you something?
Yeah...
Huh?
Wait just. One. Minute.
Look.
100 thousand, 1 million, 10 million...
100 milli–
Your bounty...
is 1.5 billion berries!
– What?!
The world looks toward the Reverie
while the crew heads toward Wano.